hi string Allen here at the
extraordinary technology 2011 it is July
29th and yesterday uh Vernon Roth gave a
very interesting presentation on hydroxy
Brown Gast H technology various names
for the similar types of processes and I
talked about transmutation of elements
toward the end and that really got my
interest everything he was saying was
very fascinating uh it's been a friend
of mine for quite a few years years um
and we we go back in in our connections
so it's an honor for me today to uh do a
recording of him I'm going to be holding
the camera uh we're we've got a side
room here so we can get some quiet and
uh just going to be ask him some
questions about these Technologies and
the opportunities that are involved with
these Technologies so uh you can read an
interview or this interview online what
we posted at PES sn.com and a date close
to the this one we'll be posting this to
YouTube and however many segments it
takes so uh here's the interview with
Vernon
Roth all right Vernon maybe you can just
really quick tell us about um your
website and just a thumbnail sketch of a
biography of you know what you do and
and where you're coming from okay well
um my first website is ancient tech.com
and that is my family site to uh to
educate and sell our uh our products
that we developed by researching ancient
technology and reproducing in our world
there's different types of elements
different creams that we produced from
ancient formulas and they have healing
effects and beneficial effects for the
body so uh check out ancient Tech that's
tek.com uh I have another website and I
actually just took control of that again
um it was very difficult to change
anything or post anything it's called
alchemical hydrogen and that's where a
lot of uh the information that I
presented yesterday and the information
I'll be talking about will is actually
going to be posted and I'll have videos
up there and such as well now that I
have uh you know control of that to uh
to post up there and that's the subject
that has me most intrigued obviously
there's a lot of things we could talk
about you've been involved in hydroxy
research for years and I have been
chasing that dream along with a lot of
other people and had been working in uh
concert with other people as well and
had been giving presentations at this
tesl Tech conference for years um but
the
alchemical
hydroxy or
hydrogen is fascinating if I could recap
it briefly you were talking about taking
the hydrogen
oxygen um in the electris process and
that somehow the in in your setup at
least you've been able to replicate the
elements that are in the water in
solution whether they're minerals or
even chemical and they actually
replicated 10 13 times uh in a given
process so you could actually um like
make copies of whatever is in the water
using this process did I summarize that
pretty well yes you summarize that very
well that's what the research is uh is
showing now that's and it's uh it's kind
of fantastical um but that's what we're
actually experiencing is this
replication of minerals and U
multiplication and I I should tell you
too that you're not the only one that
says that I've heard other people
describe that phenomena that the stuff
that was in the Joe cell and actually I
should mention that it's the Joe cell
setup using the hydroxy in the Joe cell
where this shows up um some research
Peter Stevens I think mentioned that and
others I I would say that there are at
least three other people who have
described independently that phenomena
so you weren't the first person to say
that yesterday that's great I'm really
glad that we have um independent
coroporation in that in that area
because that's really exciting I'm very
happy to hear that and that's one of the
reason why I'm not just rolling my eyes
saying I'll wait and see because now
that I've heard it enough there's
something to this you know where there's
smoke there's fire kind of thing and
another thing that's exciting about what
you're doing is you're willing to um
share this quite open openly with people
to help them do the same thing MH so uh
let's first talk about the kind of the
lay of the land maybe take five minutes
and describe how you do this and what's
going on what you have observed that
kind of a snippet from your presentation
yesterday at the tesl Tech
conference well um I start with a an
essential uh hydrogen device that I I
follow the Bob Bo method of using of
using par stainless steel plates and I
input electricity in certain ratios into
the into those plates and I don't use in
in for this process I don't use sodium
hydroxide or pottassium hydroxide as a
catalyst I rely on the natural
conductivities of different elements and
the water that I work with to be the uh
the conductor of energy and so it's not
as efficient as a conventional um uh
hydrolysis cell but we're not really
looking for huge volumes of gas here
what we're looking for is the subtle
energies and that's that's my that's my
my passionate field of research is the
subtle etheric energy that we can start
to imprint a pattern on and allow it to
manifest in the physical reality and
that's really what this comes down to is
is is finding these swirling vortexes of
ether putting a pattern into it and
finding the energy to make it a physical
reality and that's where I believe that
that's where the elements are coming
from and part of that is the a huge
portion of that is the separation of the
oxygen hydrogen allowing that to
recombine so I I know that there there
are people that experience uh
transmutation of elements in uh in the
hydrogen gas flame but now we're we're
starting to actually see that in the
hydrogen uh chamber as well so that's
what's really exciting
um my process uses stainless steel
plates and we have to vary the the the
current and voltage ratios a little bit
but we can talk about the minut of the
of the the process a little bit later um
I use the stainless steel plates and put
Energy across it and what happens is
elements that are present already in the
in the liquid start to condense and drop
out at the bottom of the device so it's
very important that the stainless steel
plates are not are not uh locked in in a
in a in a solid case but actually have
room for for liquid to flow around in
the elements to fall down in because
that's where they they accumulate and
then you can draw them off um as they
over time as they develop so that's the
basic principle and then I of course I'm
I'm very much uh safety oriented so I'm
not using a giant mason jar or something
like that I've I've blown up too many
cells to uh to play around with
plexiglass I use uh half inch to uh 3/4
inch thick uh PVC pipe and stainless
steel plates to hold everything together
and so it's very it's a very safe device
so that's what I use in particular and
then actually instead of using regular
electric power from the wall or uh U
from a from a generator I actually just
took it up to a solar panel and and and
plugged 300 watts right um yeah 300
watts will give you about uh will give
you a significant amount of uh of uh um
will give you a significant amount of
gas production my first initial
experiment I was getting I was getting
20 lers an hour off of a 45 um dollar
solar panel from uh from Harbor Freight
and it was only generating in the
neighborhood of 100 100 Watts or so so
it was kind of exciting uh to to
actually see elements being developed a
usable by product of of hydrogen gas
that we can burn later uh just coming
from the Sun with with uh the minimum of
expenses so it's really exciting so
describe the process of of uh you've got
something in solution a mineral uh that
is being
duplicated well the my see I started I
I've actually done this in another way I
do it all the time in another way based
off of an ancient technology that we
discovered and the the process is you
have a stream of hydrogen and a stream
of oxygen gas and if you have a
crystalline Matrix of whatever element
that you are
reproducing uh to form e and then you
have etheric energy an accumulator that
you direct the energy through the
crystallin Matrix pattern The
Ether and that flows into the hydrogen
and the oxygen then you have a spark
there to combine that hydrogen and
oxygen and because you've just patterned
the energy that is there the hydrogen
and oxygen form into the element that
you're after uh this kind of flies in
the face of conventional physics and uh
kind of well
okay it flies in the face of
conventional physics but you know we're
going to discover that we don't really
know a whole lot I mean even even this
last year conventional physics was
turned on its head by a couple of
discoveries when they when they uh
learned about the interaction of light
and magnetism and they said well and
they admitted in the scientific journals
they said we don't understand why this
happens all of our mathematics say that
we should be getting X number of energy
but we're getting orders of magnitude
higher than that just with the
interaction of light and magnets so
conventional physics and and our
conventional understanding of
reality is not complete and anybody who
says this is uh is just little little
arrogant there so we have to understand
that there's more to know than than than
what we know right now and we have to be
open to the information as it comes in
so uh and I actually challenge everybody
that sees this to to experiment with
this and find out if I'm right find out
if and and find out if the other people
that are that are reproducing elements
and uh and seeing the transmutation are
actually correct because I would like to
know and I want to I I want the proof
out there and I want people playing with
it because as we do the
experiments someday conventional science
will catch up and this will become
common place and 100 years from now or
maybe less than that let's hope uh they
will actually use the uh use processes
or this understanding to
uh to make the things that we need and
we won't have lack and we won't have to
we won't have mining as we understand it
now we will actually use energy to
create matter I we're talking Star Trek
technology here but that's the future
and the people that wrote that were
Visionaries so that's my that's my goal
that's what I'd like to see happen just
conceptually this is a variation of the
3D printing that they're talking about
where you put something into an AutoCAD
machine and it'll actually print out a
3D rendering of a device um that you can
then use it's a practical device yes and
the difference being that you're not
printing uh something from a set of
plans you're actually on on a nano or
molecular level you're
reproducing a a given substrate uh
that's that's so you're you're making a
copy of gold you're making a copy of
some expensive mineral or some some
expensive molecule it doesn't have to be
mineral right that's right um actually
the way I knew that I was actually
reproducing something was I was doing an
experiment with an alchemical fluid that
I make that that takes quite a long time
to make and quite and is quite an
intensive process and when I put that
into the machine and started finding
that the fluid was actually com that
that more of the fluid was coming off
the other end than I started with and it
was stronger and better than what I
started with that's when I knew that I
wasn't just reproducing a a single
element or a single mineral I was
actually reproducing a complex uh it was
actually quite a complex reproduction
and was not just uh was not just limited
to a single atom template so that was
very very exciting for me to discover
that uh because a it means that I have a
whole lot less work to do in certain
areas because it's very difficult to
produce that but also that that that
gives me a whole new um whole new
responsibility uh as we work well you
know what that's that's uh a a
psychospiritual observation that we we
go into here in the technology world but
um it's very exciting it's very exciting
to know that we don't just have to we
don't just reproduce a single element we
can actually reproduce complex elements
using energy you described uh a number
of 10 to 13 times the amount of the
original substrate being reproduced in
this process do you want to describe how
you came up with that number well that
was uh done by some friends that were
doing Joel research and they had the
conventional stainless steel tubes they
put in a a a mineral ttty Clark's
minerals Organo minerals there's
different types of minerals um they put
in a mineral ttty into this this uh this
Joe cell device which is a a very
powerful etheric energy accumulator as
well as generating hydrogen
and um they were able to through a
series of of uh boiling or generating
hydrogen and oxygen recombining it and
and starting the process all over again
they were able to actually multiply the
mineral content by 13
times and I don't know exactly where I'm
at but uh with with my experiments but
it it's a significant number up there as
well that the minerals that you start
with stay in suspension but as the the
longer you run the the there are
minerals that built or there there are
uh deposits built up at the bottom of a
Joe cell or or my device that get
thicker and thicker even though the the
the original um fluid still has all the
mineral the original mineral level in it
so you take that off and and put more
water back into it and you just keep on
building up building up the elements and
the longer you do this the more you can
multiply them so I I haven't found a
limit yet but my experiment is my
experimenting is very very new I started
this this year thinking that I was going
to give a lecture strictly about the
different uses of hydrogen in in in fuel
fuel supply Heating and cooking and uh
um uh waste remediation and then in the
process had this discovery and realized
this is really really important and
needs to get to people so I I changed my
presentation significantly and uh and
brought this here that's why um it it's
it's a it's an emerging technology and
it's it's something new that people can
experiment with but I felt like it was
really important so that's why that's
why I brought it here to present you
have some Associates you talked about
some other people the 13-fold increase
how many people do you know who have
been able to replicate
this
um doing this on purpose there aren't
very many people um I'm sure that there
are a lot of people that have discovered
this on accident
um but but doing this on purpose no
there's not not very many people there
are actually um we're actually into the
borderline alchemical field which I've
seen some amazing amazing things this
last year in and they do create elements
all the time they just don't talk about
it and they have a they have a different
system of of uh of of the uh they have a
different system than we than we're
using here but it is it is a reality
historically you talked about you own
this domain named alchemical hydrogen.
comom and you've had that domain for
quite some time and yet this particular
aspect is a new discovery what was
alchemical hydrogen before this
discovery um I was using well and I
still use hydrogen
to
uh
alchemically um destroy waste products
and I was using hydrogen to uh in in
internal combustion engines to eliminate
the exhaust and the the voc's and the
unburned hydrocarbons to keep people
from being exposed to that as well as uh
just having the engines run cleaner and
I use the word alchemical hydrogen
because we're getting into strange field
but um my life I was led to study
Alchemy and I learned about the I I
studied all the ancient techniques of
Alchemy to not only create elements but
purify the human body and and uh and
expand and uh and clean out the
Consciousness per se and then I was led
to apply that or excuse me then I was
led to to develop hydrogen technology
then I married the two together which is
uh uh that's why I called it alchemical
hydrogen because I was using an Al
alchemical fluids in the production of
hydrogen to get really phenomenal
hydrogen and and there's there's many
types of Browns gas and there some is
high Purity some is low Purity and the
different Purity levels have different
uses so if you have really high Purity
you can vaporize anything and you can
destroy tungsten and you can you can
remediate radiation and such um and but
you can't do that with with a low level
of of Browns gas you can't do it with a
low low energy but the low energy Browns
gas has different uses you can use it
for cooking can use it for you can use
it for different applications
applications that you couldn't use the
super powerful vaporizing and uh
imploding a level of Browns gas so by
applying alchemical fluid to this I
could get highle Browns gas um without
the conventional uh uh lot of uh without
the conventional resonance and the
electrical circuits and stuff like that
I could I could generate the the high
level Brown gas without um using the
expensive equipment or I could vary the
levels of the fluids and get the
low-level Browns gas that I could use
for other processes so that's why I
called it alchemical hydrogen because I
was using this fluid in different
locations and such um so that's where
the that's where the name came from okay
well I think it's pous that you grabb
that domain name and now you have this
totally new process that I think fits
the name even better wouldn't you say
absolutely and except it's not just
hydrogen it's Hy and oxygen from a brown
gas process but Hydro I mean that that's
a good name still it is it is uh we
actually there's actually four times the
amount of oxygen than there is hydrogen
so well four times the volume excuse me
um but yes it it it is fortuitous I'm
very glad that it happened in terms of
rolling this out into a practical
application where people can actually do
this on a commercial scale M um how
close do you think you are or someone
could be you you could you know and
you're willing to train people you're
willing to you know some somebody comes
along and say hey could you show me how
to do this you're glad to do it yeah I
am and you're very um sharing that way
it's it's really quite phenomenal um I
would plug in here though something I
don't think Vernon would say that if he
does help you make sure you remember him
in any kind of uh you know Revenue that
you're making on this that you you know
volunteer some kind of royalty that goes
back to him to help his research because
this is just one of many things that
he's playing with he's extremely
prolific as an inventor and an intuitive
in the scientific field and so I think
he deserves that kind of uh Su
sustainment but answer the question of
how close and what would it take to um
there's obviously a whole whole bunch of
different applications of this but what
would be the lwh hanging fruit and how
hard would it be or easy easy would it
be to get to that lanan fruit
well the the easiest way to go about
this would be to have uh to just create
a little device and and these things
could go into a 5 gallon bucket if you
wanted to be really low Tech and uh and
put it together or like I do I use the
uh the the the heavy duty uh CPVC
plastic and stainless steel um but the
easiest way to do this would be to just
build a device and hook it up to a solar
panel and start dropping out the
elements and finding an uh an Avenue
that you could sell it or um or use the
elements in some in some way
so I I'm very I'm very much into uh
people being self-sufficient so let's
say you Sterling wanted to wanted to set
this up at your house and you could
start generating power and you got a
little shed in the backyard hooked up to
and you got a solar patter mounted on it
then you just be using the sun using a
passive energy source to to uh develop a
a uh a monetized stream okay let's just
say that and so you have that set up at
your place and your neighbor can have
one set up to actually put it into a
production level I I I'm not a huge fan
of of of big corporations getting
control of things and they don't like to
have anything that they don't you know
have an iron fisted control over so um
but if you had a group of people that
could put it into production you'd have
you know a piece of property with with a
bunch of solar panels set up and a bunch
of hydrogen devices there that are just
you know generating the uh generating
the elements and generating a a usable
energy source so that's that's the the
the probably the fastest way and the
easiest way to start to move this into
the uh move this into the uh the
production level that you that you
talked
about you were talking about um taking a
chemical type of element
molecule that you had developed and you
found it showing up in large quantities
and that was the indicator to you that
something was happening uh reproduction
wise or alchemical wise how hard would
it be to isolate these things uh once
you've created
them well uh it's just a matter of uh
of on an individual level it'd be a
matter of some chemistry I have a friend
that uh takes our
alchemical gold and uses a little uses a
little bit of chemistry process on it
and creates gold chloride which he then
sells to a chemical company gold
chloride is an industrial uh um it's a
it's what we call a precious chemical if
you're working with precious metals uh
for to to actually create a revenue
stream it's it's easier to work with
precious chemicals rather than precious
metals because they're at least four
times more expensive than the metals so
if you're working with um gold chloride
it's not $1,600 an ounce it's um in the
neighborhood of uh uh it's neighborhood
of $6,000 for a high an ounce for high
Purity gold chloride and it's funny
because the process of dropping gold out
from a from a mining process you go
through the gold chloride stage and then
you go into the yellow metal and
everybody wants the yellow metal but
that's Gold Fever if you stick with the
gold chloride you have a a completely
different uh you have a completely
different level of monetary income same
thing with silver Silver's uh I don't
but let's say silver was uh $10 an ounce
uh silver nitrate or or some of the
different uh precious chemicals from
Silver actually are four times that
amount four to 10 times that amount if
you if you can uh create the right type
and then and people sell a chemist sell
that and and make a significant amount
of money more than the uh more than the
the metal itself so the process so
dropping out these elements would be to
find the proper uh proper place to to to
move it and that would involve a little
bit of chemistry and selling it to to
chemist shop or you could use I I hadn't
thought of this before you could use an
electroplated process and um plate this
metal onto a uh onto a substrate and
then just sell that and there wouldn't
be chemistry involved at all so there's
different ways not being a not being an
actual chemist I I haven't explored all
all those options um just been really
busy you know working with the
technology so but people turning this
into a cottage industry could find a
local um substance that's expensive that
they could um Implement into this
process to replicate it and and sell it
locally we're we're suffering from a
huge uh
uh and people don't know about it very
much yet but we're actually suffering
from a huge deficiency in uh in the rare
Earths right now Rare Earth are very
important for the uh for the rare of
course rare earth magnets but also the
batteries that are being developed theum
for example exactly and so if you can
create a a stream of the rare Earth's uh
those elements then you'd be uh you'd be
sitting pretty would that would actually
be a much better way to go than than
worrying about the uh worrying about the
the elements gold and such because from
an alchemicals perspective I have to
throw this out there um an alchemist is
forbidden from making a profit with gold
they can use it to further their
research they can use it to keep
themselves alive but if they try to
elevate their status in life with gold
they will be it'll end some of them die
some of them are are severely punished
by the universe so it's like a spiritual
um calling so to speak to be an
alchemist absolutely and you have you
can't be in it for greed you can't be in
it for control or manipulating if you if
your motives are pure than you can be an
alchemist so it's just a warning about
getting into alchemy that you have to be
a good person and stay that way ABS
absolutely absolutely interesting now
let's talk I could actually talk even
more about that but that gets really
esoteric but I've seen some things this
last year that are really interesting
but we won't talk about that we can talk
about that another time okay what about
let's talk about what kind of process
you would be um in looking at to get set
up um just first of all to replicate it
to prove to yourself that this is real
how many what's the expense of materials
and time to replicate and to see that
the effect does work well um first thing
is you start out with stainless steel
plates uh 316 I always work with 316
stainless there are other materials and
different things that you can play with
but the most rly available 316 stainless
in uh I I like 6x6 squares but whatever
you're working with whatever size
material vessel you're working with so I
use uh 8 and 1/2 in well 8 in nominal
CPVC pipe and seal it closed with these
things inside me so 6x6 works pretty
well for that and you have um these here
with you at the conference maybe what we
could do is after this episode we could
um have you actually pull it apart and
show us the different components in it
could we do that I yeah we can do that I
can you can videotape uh some of the the
devices themselves and you can take a
look at them no problem so um estimate
about how much money you're would would
the components cost materials just to
just to start out to play with it
probably figure about $1
$150 um you've got to cut the stainless
steel plates um I have some if you guys
if somebody wants to to I have a whole
bunch of them of the 6x6 squares if
somebody wants to buy some I just have
you know just the money into the uh the
shearing it but if you guys want to just
buy stainless steel plates and Shear
them off that's uh whatever if you've
got a machine shop local that can do
that um that works pretty well back in
my Joe cell days when I was really
focused on that um there was quite a bit
of
um talk about when you cut the metal
that you get some
um magnetization of the metal going on
do you have to be careful about that
kind of stuff um the
using a conventional Joe cell which has
the concentric stainless steel tubes you
do have to worry about that uh that's
actually fairly easy to overcome with
Browns gas because you can you can heat
it and take out the take out the
magnetism uh shearing it or uh or
cutting this cutting the shapes out with
a uh with a water jet is uh because I
use I use flat parallel plates instead
of the concentric stainless steel tubes
um because I can control control the the
the distances much better um so when you
share them there's there's less of an
issue with that uh plus you know there's
magnetism there's paramagnetism and then
there's
diamagnetism and so I one of the
actually couple of the free energy
devices that I've seen actually uh
relies Upon A Rao between the three
levels of magnetism both paramagnetism
diamagnetism and magnetism
in in varying ratios and when they were
able to tune the machines to not just
the components but everything around the
machine to the ratios of uh more
paramagnetism than than the others but
but different ratios they were able to
achieve free energy so some some amount
of magnetism is good I haven't actually
run into an issue where the magnetism in
the system is is a detriment right now
because I don't work with the
conventional they're the con the uh
concentric stainless steel too
so and the concentric um tubes are
usually what you see in a Joe cell so a
Joe cell is not necessary for this it's
one of the things where it shows up but
it's not necessarily A crucial
component um Let me let me back up here
the conventional Joe cell that we see
which is the conventional or the
concentric stainless steel tubes is a
simp is one type of Jose
if you look at uh the books that have
been written on Joe cell technology and
I actually gave a lecture on this about
5 years ago if you look at the the the
books and the information on that what
you're really looking for is um certain
types of materials interacting with
other types of materials so you're
looking for metallic and this this also
goes back to orgon research you're
looking for metallic versus natural
materials um some Joo cells I have a I
have a battery it literally looks like a
battery it's made out of brass plates
and a different type of fluid in there
and it is and it conforms to all the
rules of a Joe cell it's just not made
out of a concentric tube or or like the
Mojo cell a sphere which is really fun
to play with um but it but it actually
conforms to all the rules of the Joe
cell certain ratios to height to width
and the fluid the fluid in there versus
the metal that it's interacting with so
there are different types of Joe cells
the the concentric tube is only is only
one of them
so um is this going to be a science
where you can follow a recipe um
and like for example if you were to mass
produce something like this you can make
it the same way every time and it works
the same way every time or is there
something that goes into some materials
where you require a gift to do some
tuning an alchemical gift for example I
haven't run into that actually I on this
in this aspect it's behaving the same
way each time and I'm not I I'm not
running into you know times of day I'm
not running into the attitude of the
operator which I I have machines that
are that that uh that work absolutely
contingent on the attitude and the
spiritual mindset of the operator um but
this is this is behaving in a little bit
different way and I think we've it it's
a refinement of the process that allows
us to focus the the energy without
worrying about without worrying too much
about uh the outside extraneous input
now um I haven't I can't rule out the
zodiacal signs or where the Moon is
which um uh is actually very important
um in some processes in some process
it's important in a lot of scientific
processes they
cannot machine the plutonium cores for
nuclear uh nuclear bombs or nuclear
reactors uh they cannot machine them
under certain signs of the Moon because
if they do the the metal will literally
change
Dimensions as the moon shifts they have
to they have to machine them under
certain signs that are what they call
fixed otherwise the metal will change
dimensions and not work properly and
this is talked about in in people who
are in that industry um it is it is a
little known fact in the industry yes
something they don't dare talk about
absolutely to most people because it
kind of fly kind of flies in the face of
conventional
physics
so um that's a that's a very strange and
uh very uh little little known uh little
known secret of the nuclear industry I
understand people who make automobile
parts or like engines for example for
race cars uh that when they make they
can make three engines under seemingly
identical uh circumstances but they have
to test each one of them because they
don't actually function the same that's
amazing and it has to do with when they
were made and and it's there's really no
such thing as two identical
scientifically made things because there
are other phenomena going on it's not
just humans that are uh responsive to
astrological types of influences that
materials also have an input but you're
saying believe that absolutely in this
particular process um you haven't
noticed yet that kind of influence well
I haven't noticed that yet on a on a on
a macrocosmic scale that may be
happening on a microcosmic scale but I
haven't noticed it on a macrocosmic
scale you know it's funny you mentioned
that because when I was in uh studying
electrical engineering they told us the
same thing about things like solar
panels and integrated circuits and they
actually have to put in um they actually
have to engineer in adjustments so that
they can tune something into the the
behavior pattern that they want
and um from a from a religious
perspective we we see that um all energy
has Consciousness and if we're working
with certain types of energy we have to
understand that that the uh that the
consciousness of that energy is going to
come into play but on a macrocosmic
scale with this hydrogen system that
I've been working with and uh we're not
seeing a we're not seeing a lot of uh
influence in that regard which makes me
happy because uh because it means that
that everybody can work with it and
everybody can play with it so it's
that's exciting so it may not be
necessary that the person have an
alchemical calling so to speak to do
this or do you think how important do
you think that would
be well you know we're going to find out
that out in the next six months because
I'm I'm very much alchemically oriented
and so I'm probably not the uh not the
norm of the people that are going to be
that are going to be working with this I
learned something very interesting um
conventional engineering deals with the
bell curve okay they want to know what
goes on in this in this normal space
okay and they plot all their diagrams
and everything and they create bell
curves because they want to understand
what goes on in this normal space I
realized that is so far outside of my
Keen of understanding because I don't
care what goes on there because that's
that's normal I want to know why this
little Spike occurred over here I want
to know know what goes on outside of the
norm so that that's that's funny uh a
funny way to look at it but that's
that's where I'm at and turn that into a
new Norm mhm honing on that mhm MH
absolutely yeah so we didn't finish the
question about uh what would be involved
in getting started in this just on on a
replication basis to prove to yourself
that it works uh we talked about
materials what about time
um well if you're mechanically or or uh
um if you're Hands-On oriented it you
know about a week to put this all
together a week fulltime or tinkering
time a week tinkering time yeah hobby
time in the evening when you come home
from work yeah exactly hobby time and
just playing around with it um you can
sit and put together the you can sit and
put together the plates pretty easily um
there there are certain rules you have
to follow and so you know you don't one
see this is the this is the thing about
working with working with hydrogen you
follow the rules until you understand
the rules and you learn where you can
break them okay but you when you when
you first start out you reproduce things
exactly the way they were made before
once you understand the rules then you
can start experimenting outside of the
rules do you have on your website some
kind of a set of plans no nothing
nothing's I just have a few pictures up
there right now I just literally just
barely got control of that website again
from uh from the person that was running
it before so real good guy but he kind
of disappeared down in Mexico and uh is
exploring the uh the ancient ruins down
there which makes it very difficult to
you know run a computer and Upstate
websites so I just got control of that
so I can post so I can start changing
content again okay and
uh
let's do you want to give your contact
information or can people go to the
website to get that uh people can go to
the website my the easiest way to
contact me is either through Facebook or
my email um earth's earth's
Ransom
yahoo.com that's e a r t HS R A NS o m
yahoo.com or just look me up on Facebook
I communicate that way pretty easily too
okay those are the easiest
ways yeah I I tempted to to uh bring up
what you posted on Facebook the other
day about 6ot
rattles well you know uh I have I have
been blessed with different Messengers
through my through my life and I was
attacked by a six foot rattlesnake the
other day that was a pretty uh pretty
interesting experience and uh it struck
at me twice and missed both times so
it's a it's a beautiful little miracle
that I I'm here and um but that was a
that was a sign of change and actually
in retrospect that was an interesting
little warning that I that I received so
um I I'm glad that it happened you know
I I did have to kill the rattlesnake but
because it was very aggressive and uh
was not just you know hanging out by
himself and doing nothing he was
actually very aggressive so um it was a
it was a an indicator that certain
things were changing for me so which
happens last time was a bear 5 years ago
broke into my
house teaching an interesting lesson
that I had to uh that I had to learn so
interesting well thanks for sharing that
is there anything else in this
particular um sector that uh we haven't
talked about that ought to be brought up
uh you know I'm sure there is but we uh
but as as you know when we started
looking at the machine and such I'll uh
I'll start thinking of more stuff that
need presented but yeah all right um so
let's do that as part three okay and uh
we'll we'll stop this segment for now
all right sounds good
hi Sterling Allen here and we're at the
Tesla Tech Conference 2011 in albu CRI
New Mexico July
2019th and uh I'm with Vernon Roth here
this is actually the second part of a
twart uh video series the first part
we'll have a link there in the bottom in
this YouTube video where you can see
where he described this alchemical
process where in his uh electrolysis
scenario he's found that some of the uh
elements that are in the water in
certain electrolysis scenarios are
duplicated whether they're minerals or
whether they are chemicals chemical
compounds and the question I didn't ask
him was what about molecules like
insulin for example could you he he
found that elements that are within the
water are duplicated so that if you
start with one part in some cases he he
saw with the uh cycling of the water
they actually had 13 times as much of
that element at the end than they had at
the beginning and this is true with gold
uh particles um and with some fairly
complex chemical compounds that that he
describ that's in part A we we went
through all that kind of the philosophy
behind it and uh the part this video
here is to describe the apparatus he's
actually agreed to go ahead and take
things apart and show us exactly how he
makes this not exactly I mean this is
going to be fairly technical um but you
know it's not like he's going to show
you you know A to Z but he is going to
give us uh a good overview going through
each component and now that I've given
that explanation I would like to go
ahead and turn it over I'm going to go
ahead and and control the camera um but
I'd like Veron to recap what I just said
in his words to begin with and uh then
we'll we'll make this cut this video
into however segments we need to as Part
B of this series okay all right let's go
for
it well thank you Sterling and thank you
for everybody for being here and we're
going to move on
forward so I think that
uh one of the most important things that
we can you know that we can do with our
um energy and for the future is to find
out more and uh better ways to use water
in our world and that's really a huge
portion of my research as many of you
have experienced the the spark of Life
water and its various incarnations and
what that what it's used for
um that's uh really my driving F force
is to find out different ways to use
water in the world and so that's what I
do with hydrogen and I make hydrogen and
oxygen from uh from electricity and
water so that's what we're talking about
here and this is a basic cell this is
what we call a dry cell hey before you
get into the
um this is actually take two the first
one we thought the camera was rolling
and it wasn't um tell us about what
happened with um after you gave your
presentation two people came up to you
oh um uh yesterday after I gave my
presentation uh two people independently
came up to me and said uh we also have
experienced the multiplication of
elements that uh we we did not expect at
all using energy magnetic fields and uh
geometric structures and it's occurring
on a much on a much smaller scale than
what we're experiencing here but it is
occurring and so they said we are so
glad that uh that someone else talked
about it because now we know that we're
not crazy now that we now we know that
this is actually reality so it's very
exciting stuff and this is going to I
feel like it's going to be happening
more and more and many people may
already actually be doing it not knowing
what's going on so with that said we
will start with um we'll start with
hydrogen and why don't we start where
started and what we have over here is a
conventional uh well it uses um some
principles of Bob boy's uh work with
hydrogen it uses some principles of uh
of um George wisman and U Brown's work
with hydrogen it's a simple hydrogen
cell with parallel stainless steel
plates in it you input 120 volts DC and
this is not supposed to be in there
that there and the gas comes out of the
hydrogen unit goes into the reservoir
which acts like a uh a trap in an
expansion chamber to trap Vapors and
then the gas feeds from the
reservoir into a first stage bubbler
which is this is a safety bubbler and it
and it also serves as as a a wash for
the gas to wash off any sodium hydroxide
and then the gas escapes out the top and
this little hose you see down at the
bottom is the water feed to the um
hydrogen device so gas and a little bit
of water comes out here and the water
returns to the bottom and and and fills
the device this is a small device it
well not not a not a very small device
but it's a uh it's a simple device
excuse me and this was uh commissioned
by a friend of mine to run a uh to help
run his diesel generator on his uh his
Mountain retreat and it uses a solar
panels a set of solar panels about uh
about 1,000 watts of solar panel goes
into this and boosts his hydrogen or
boosts his diesel engine um once it
leaves that just on a tangent what kind
of improvements does he see on the
diesel generator using that well what we
calculated was that uh because there is
no parasitic drag from an alternator to
feed his uh to feed his engine using
this and one other piece of technology
that's not mine so I can't talk about it
but it's a passive device uh he we
calculated that he will get about a 90%
boost in his diesel generator system so
solar power it's almost a double of his
almost almost a double absolutely and
then that's taken into account the
wattage from the solar panels yes that T
it's like a voltage multiplier we're
using you were using water instead of uh
uh and we're using water in hydrogen um
that is not what you're going to get if
you have a parasitic drag and you're
running it off of your own generator
that's just with the solar panels but he
found that it was cheaper for him to do
that and use a generator as his existing
power source than it was to to install a
big solar system with batteries and all
the electrical components that would go
along with that this is more plug-and
playay for him and he and he likes that
so that's what this one is built for
with 1,000 watt um solar panel he was
able to power his house 1,000 watts and
and a diesel generator and a diesel
generator right a diesel generator right
so he's running his house on the diesel
generator with a 1,000 watt solar panel
right essentially okay and 90 and and
10% of the normal fuel is this
augmenting so he had he's also plugged
into the Grid or is he off grid uh he
will be off grid once he goes this way
because his electricity will be cheaper
with this method than it will be off of
the conventional uh grid system so this
is uh also what I brought to to uh show
a a a simple system the most simple
system that you can uh that you can deal
that you can create hydrogen device
Reservoir bubbler and this is very safe
and it's uh excuse me and it's got a lot
of safeties built in especially at the
end when the water or when the hydrogen
comes out of there and goes into here
this is our flashback arrester and and
the last line of defense uh for this
system which it's filled with water and
it bubbles through it and then the gas
goes to the generator if we were running
a
torch we were going to run a torch say
for welding in a welding
shop one more system would be installed
here and that is this uh flashback
arrester and and this is something off
the shelf this is something off the
shelf you buy them for $40 to $60 a pair
you get it at any welding shop I
recommend I highly recommend it um and
it's called a flashback arrest it's
called a flashback or a spark back
arrest
um they use them for oxygen and the
suddening Torches as well as hydrogen
torches as well so that's what I
recommend on this system down here are
you using any kind of uh conditioning of
the DC that's coming into it are you
using no we're not it's straight line DC
and I went with uh I went with straight
line DC because it's easier to work with
the only current control that I that I
uh put in the system is the number of
plates and the uh concentration of of of
catalyst
when I started working with this I
started working with the electronic
gizmos and the and the pulse width
modulators and all that burned them up
pretty quick in my experimental phase
and
realized um I wanted something a little
bit more foolproof and so I developed a
a way of calculating number of plates to
the current ratios that I wanted and
also uh the Catalyst uh the amount of
catalyst in the system could help
control the current flow did we go over
those numbers this morning we have not
yet and so I was going to I was going to
outline that cuz I I can illustrate it
very easily with these okay um but
essentially I I'll just give you the
numbers right now uh maximum
2.23 volts per
cell
maximum uh
one4 uh watt or excuse me 1/4 amp per
square in of plate surface so for
instance we we have a 6x6 plate here so
that's 36 square in and if we were using
this the 6x6 not including the ring in
here just ignore that if we were using
the 6x6 plate putting current across
that our our limit would be 9 amps
because excuse me uh 9 / 36 is of course
4 so that's our uh4 amp per square in
that's the maximum amount I actually
like to run about uh about if if using
that plate I like to run about 5 amps
just to make certain that there's a a
nice uh nice margin of safety there so
whether you had two plates or 100 plates
you go based on one surface you're not
going to exceed this cell system that's
right by 5 amp by by 9 amps that's right
exactly now this system you know we we
we'll get into that so we've got um if
we were using these plates we would go
uh 9 amps since the since we've actually
cut off surface area in this device I go
less than 9 amps and then we go to uh
2.35 volts or 2.34 volts per cell so
there's no more than 2.3 no more because
you'll start to burn up your plates mhm
okay so there's 1 2 3 4 five six cells
in there so you would not go more than
and 14 Volts for the lay person I'm I'm
seeing you know at 24 so what you
calling this is a this is a double unit
okay there's a there's a negative plate
in the center and a positive plate on
one side and a positive plate on the
other so what you're actually seeing is
two uh two sets of hydrogen uh uh a two
stacked hydrogen device and so going
from this side to this side what are you
calling a cell the cell is the different
distance between plates so there's 1 2 3
4 5 six cells in there and then we go to
the other
side 1 2 3 4 5 oh I'm sorry there's uh
no there's six yeah that's six okay six
so there's six on each side with a with
a with a negative Center so there's a a
positive and a negative positive on the
outside two sets of positive negative 12
piece of metal makes a six cell
yeah and this this appears to be the
conventional cell that you can buy on
almost any hydrogen device but it's not
and we'll get into the difference but we
have we have two
inputs fuel in or excuse me water in
hydrogen
out 13 what's plates 13 say what 13
plates yeah there's 13 plates there oh
there's 13 pieces of metal yeah 13
pieces of metal uh negative in the
center and you can see I slip on a
little or neutral negative you call
neutral neutral are the ones in between
the negative and the positive okay you
just put on a little Spade connector on
the bottom slip it on and uh um and then
the positive go up there on the little a
little Spade connector on the edges I
sell this for about for uh 300 bucks
this is actually my breather unit I use
this to um breathe Brown's gas but we'll
get into that as we as we move forward
so that is the essential uh that is
essentially what we're dealing with here
only and that one is a larger scale so
there's uh there's uh 60 plates in that
device with a nice nice little water
jacket on either side to make certain
things stay
cool and 60 plates takes 120 volts so
that's 2 volts per cell so uh or you
know thereabouts and on that one we're
dealing with a little bit larger larger
plates so I can actually go up to 12
amps per per uh per um excuse me 12 amps
for the whole unit because there the the
plates are actually larger so for the
voltage it's additive for the number of
cells that's right and for amp it's it's
uh based on the surface of one single
cell right as far as what Max we're in a
series system so it's the it's the the
amperage is based off of one plate
versus the uh the voltage being based
off of the entire set of plates okay so
that's a little bit of the
technicalities that we uh we go into
with this with this type of hydrogen
device um and these are these are rules
that have been tried out many tried and
proven many times if you go over
amperage you'll start to crystallize
your plates and they won't produce gas
very well if you go over voltage you'll
start to uh break down your uh you
you'll start to break down your plates
and you don't and you don't want that
and let me ask you just quickly talking
about um the Alchemy uh principle that
we were talking about this morning
um of these two systems have you um have
you achieved what we're calling Alchemy
or the multiplication of elements within
the water in either one of these or both
in these two systems we do that system I
don't want that to happen I don't want
mul I don't want uh minerals or elements
to multiply because there's no way for
real way for them to get out this system
is a standalone system I have systems
like that that have been running for
years so we'll want to talk about when
you don't want it what to do to prevent
it right well what you do to prevent
it what you do to prevent it is uh use
distilled water and sodium hydroxide and
a few little Catalyst you buy my
electric water throw that in there that
can eliminate what we call uh CO2
soaking uh CO2 soaking is when your is
when your uh your hydrogen device runs
down and the plates are covered with a
CO2 layer and you start to see a black
uh film developing that some that
sometimes there other colors and that uh
actually starts to uh starts to reduce
your efficiency by using the electric
water and some of the the the the
catalysts that that we've created uh
using the gold and the platinum and such
you completely eliminate CO2 soaking
this unit runs better after 6 months
than it does when it's brand new okay
cuz it runs better the longer it goes
unlike like most systems which suffer
from CO2 soaking and a couple of other
uh ailments that start to clog up their
plates so uh that's that's what you use
frequencies for usually is to is to
strip that off uh but I don't like the
use of frequencies uh so much as I like
the use of
catalysts and so that that for a very
simple system with very um minimal uh
Catalyst or
maintenance that's quite a well the
Catalyst never the Catalyst never really
wears out because we have the reservoirs
that feed the Catalyst back to the
machine okay so the catus never really
wears out the catus is always being
recycled how often are you U measuring
the P the ratio or the um
concentration
um once I put it in there I don't
usually uh it it doesn't really change
well that's one thing that I will talk
about when we start multiplying the
minerals is that when you use uh uh
heavy acids or heavy Alkali that for
some reason that actually uh inhibits
the process of multiplication and uh
what we want to do over here so we'll
get we'll get into that a little bit
more and by the way if other people in
the audience have questions that you
want to ask you think ought to be um
brought up at any point feel
free so like I said this is theem this
is a basic system and this type of
system can run for for incredible
amounts of time I put them on semi trcks
I put them on oil Wells I put them on
Standalone generators that type of thing
because they're they're bomb proof and
they're they're very very sturdy so uh I
like the this is what we call this is a
dry
cell this will you'll see is a wet cell
and this is a hybrid it's got plates
that are pressed together with a spacer
in between and so there's not a lot of
room for um uh water to get or there's
not a lot of uh ease of uh communication
for water and there but it slowly seeps
and fills up all the cells so that's
kind of a hybrid system uh it's lined
with Teflon inside there to make certain
that it's uh very very heat resistant oh
there's one thing I really want to
stress if you're building a hydrogen
device hydrogen boils at 100 or excuse
me 210 or water boils at
210° inside of a hydrogen device water
boils at
140° okay it's a completely different
environment inside there
so if your if your device is running
hotter than 140 150° you're actually
boiling water and creating Steam and
that's very dangerous especially for an
engine not so dangerous for a torch
that's okay but for an engine that's
really bad so be aware of that that's
why these also serve as as uh Safety
Systems to keep any uh any Steam from uh
getting into the engine so that's uh
that's a little Preparatory part
remember um 2.35 volts per
cell uh one4 amp per square in and that
is a pretty good round number to uh to
remember as you're as you're building
your devices where did you come up with
those numbers um
those those I I studied a long time with
Bob Boyce and I read a a huge amount by
uh by George wisman and um y Brown and
those were the numbers that I found fit
the the the uh the criteria the best and
they've proven out over and over again
if you if you go over current you'll
crystallize your plates and stop
producing gas you may get a lot of gas
it won't be great gas and over time the
plates will start producing so your so
your efficiency on your hydrogen device
will go down if you go over voltage your
plates will start falling apart okay oh
we bought so many devices we bought
round devices and my family and I and we
played with with a lot of different
devices and we found every single which
way to fail I we we got a tube device
they were using uh baking soda as the
Catalyst we ran that thing like they
said we could but at at a at a at a peak
output we ran it for about uh four or
five maybe a week but I think it was
about four or five days pulled that
thing apart it fell in half because the
plates had just eaten themselves to
death um baking soda not a good way to
go
in my opinion I don't I don't know
anybody else maybe somebody else has a
fantastic experience with it
but but the longterm in harsh conditions
this seems to be the best way to go um
moving right along uh one of my one of
my fields of research is Health and
Longevity as as as we've already uh
mentioned with the uh with the different
Waters that that my family and I've
created and so I wanted to find a way to
uh deliver
um beneficial elements and such to the
body uh more more quickly and
effectively and I turned to my hydrogen
research because Yule Brown when he was
doing his work he could send divers down
supplied with a supply of Brown's gas he
could send divers down twice as deep and
come up two or three times as fast as a
regular diver because the hydrogen and
oxygen was was going into the cells the
oxygen was uh was O um giving the needed
oxygen to the tissues and then the
oxygen hydrogen was recombining as water
and not producing any toxic gases in the
body so they could come up faster
without any bends so uh and then there
were several gentlemen as a matter of
fact um uh some of the people here have
actually done work with healing and and
uh curing of chronic dis or working with
at least relieving chronic diseases
using Browns gas and I I'd read many of
these accounts and so I was very very
excited so I studied and created a
device
that allows me to use no sodium
hydroxide at all and and instead use
just the either the etheric elements or
the ormous elements that I work with and
breathe those substances and that's what
this this start this turned out to be
and you put you put uh water in with
with a little
Reservoir the uh gas comes out and you
can breathe that directly
and excuse me oh boy howy it's good
stuff gets rid of
headaches um there's talk of actually
people putting plastic bags over
sprained wrists and such and and and
healing the uh healing the injuries even
uh even stroke victims so there's a lot
of uh there's a lot we could go go
pretty deep into that but we don't
that's this is not the Forum um but what
I noticed was when I added an alchemical
fluid to this this system right here uh
the alchemical fluid that was very very
difficult to make make and and took a
long time to produce uh suddenly was
multiplying it got thicker and darker in
the in the uh in the reservoir I said
wait a minute that shouldn't be
happening I I've worked for years to try
and figure out a faster way to make this
so and when I analyzed it I realized oh
look there's it's it's actually
concentrating it's actually more
concentrated than when I started so at
that point I I remembered some
experiments that were done and realized
that it's possible that I was actually
multiplying um chemical compounds and
multiplying elements so should I um tell
that story or should we just go let's
just go on with this here yeah we they
can go to part one because we talked
that about that in part one didn't we
yes that's right we did so we're good
okay okay so let me show you what I did
here now you're going to what you
actually see here is a violation of the
rules that I already laid down but
that's because we're not using sodium
hydroxide we're using less plates
and we actually end up giving it a
little bit more um we actually end up
giving it a little bit more
voltage what you see here is a
conventional I know it's very dirty but
but that's good good elements that you
see in there I drained out most of it
you can see some of the red red stuff
down there
um excuse me this was all completely
clear when I started and it's a it's a
system that uses no sodium hydroxide
because as I said sodium hydroxide
interferes with the um interferes with
the process and and I know people seeing
the video are saying well look at that
red stuff he's disintegrating plates I'm
not disintegrating plates I have
measured all of these things with
micrometers and I'm not disintegrating
the plates at all I'm actually
multiplying and dropping out elements
and so what you see here is essentially
this system a little bit different
voltage current ratios this is my first
system that I ran off of a solar panel
literally what you're seeing here this
device generates about about 20 L an
hour
using is my solar pan right there
hydrogen an hour 20 20 L of hydrogen an
hour using only a little
$45 solar panel from Harbor Freight okay
how many square feet is it
uh probably about uh four and 1 half
five okay 4 and2 5 ft it's not even
their big their big powerful one this is
just an experiment I did and that I
haven't measured the output from when I
hooked it up to the big big panels but
the uh the little solar panel is
generating about 20 lers an hour so
about a third of a liter a minute and so
we've got here we have h a fuel that we
can use to cook our food heat our houses
it's being generated by the Sun and at
the same time it's creating a byproduct
of an AC sellable uh element of gold and
platinum and stuff like that so that's
the the basic the basics of it now what
I what you have to do you can't see it
in there very well so what I'm going to
do is I'm going to hold this here
essentially you put together a set of
stainless steel plates with spacers here
I use an
O-ring or actually it's a quad ring it
gives me twice as much surface area of
contact than an O-ring but that's
another story um here I use an o-ring in
here I use a strip here and a strip here
and allow free communication of water
down and up so that that way the
minerals and elements that are
multiplied can fall down and the gas
from the Hy the hydrogen and oxygen gas
can Rise And so there's so it's
completely unobstructed in this system
it's contained so that of course it
doesn't leak and the gas comes out the
top so that's basically what I have
inside there like a w what's that like a
wet it is a wet cell this is what is
considered a wet cell system we're not
looking for high efficiency in here you
said there's a basically along each side
could you point out where those are it
looks like you have little spacers right
about there and right about there yeah
there's there's some spacers right about
there and uh once again I violated the
rules I didn't go an e/ inch of spacing
I literally just used a uh I'm so
ashamed I used zip
ties I cut zip ties and used those as a
spacers because they're a little bit
less than a 16th of an inch see in this
system we're putting our energy into
making the the elements and we're not uh
we're not concerned about super high
efficiency like with my hydrogen device
so we can play with some of the the
variables so and also you want to play
with more heat as you neutrals say again
you want to play with more heat as you
have less neutrals yes I have less less
neutrals so as he said more heat is
generated and more um there there's a
little bit different current ratio so in
this one here's the numbers I've got a
positive a negative plate and 1 2 3
four uh four neutrals so 1 2 3 four five
cells five cells on each side so for a
total of 10 cells and I run about 16
Volts for uh for 3 amps maximum into
here with a power supply and what that
does is that that drops out such a huge
amount of elements like I said all the
water was completely clear when I
started and the plates are not
disintegrating I take this apart
routinely and uh well every month every
uh uh couple weeks or so measure the
plates I'm not disintegrating the plates
I'm actually dropping out elements out
of the water so you talked about you've
got some kind of a gasket or sealing
this is my this is my favorite sealing
material I have tried so many I have
tried
EPDM I bua uh nitril
my favorite seiling material is uh is a
Teflon rope it's very similar to the
Teflon tape you put on threads to when
you thread something in just like you
use just like I used here to thread this
in place
um yeah the Teflon tape there uh but
it's but it's actually been uh been spun
into a long cord and that is one of the
best sealing materials ever and it's
called Teflon rope it well Teflon rope
uh some places call it uh a Teflon
gasket material it's it's somewhat
expensive you know I was a little bit
loathed to open this but but I figured
hey you know what we need to do it you
said it was about 20 bucks for that
piece there uh not really it's probably
closer to 10 yeah I probably between $10
and $12 so um I'm just and how often are
you opening this up if you're using it
for um well you don't have to open it up
if you're if you're using it you don't
have to open it up I open it up because
I'm in the experimenting phase I wanted
to check and see the the uh the plates I
wanted to see what was going on in here
but if you're doing Alchemy and you're
dropping stuff out don't you need to get
in there to access it that's what this
is for this is bottom access you just um
the elements collect in here I just undo
that drain them off into a into a a
gallon jug and pour another gallon jug
in and start over so I don't have to I
don't have to open this at all once it's
uh once it's sealed up these these
connections here what's what's that
about oh that's just uh okay here
here's this is the gas out as gas
accumulates in here gas comes out here
and
escapes and this is the water in this
can be hooked up to a reservoir I just
connected it to itself for to transport
here okay so so this connection is not
the way you want to do it in the
completed unit you did this for the sake
of Transport yeah for transport usually
this thing connects to a reservoir that
it goes from here and here to a
reservoir and then goes out I just put
this together so I could carry it here
and didn't have something flopping
around to transport um but this is but
you could do it this way you could do it
this way you could just unscrew that
pour out your elements plug it back in
and pour your water in or pour your
water in through here and it would fill
up okay um so it's it's very simple very
user friendly once it's sealed you don't
have to take it apart once it's sealed
it's fine I take it apart because I'm in
the experimental phase I want to test
what it looks like in here it's got jled
around a little bit um I'm going to I'm
going to build a a much stronger unit
that is uh that is actually epoxy
together so uh here in the future but
maybe you can these look like off the
shelf components here what what are you
using here okay these are uh this is
CPVC do not use PVC pipe PVC pipe goes
up to about 160° fit CPVC can go up to
uh 210 220
um if you're running that hot there's
something wrong but I'm a huge fan of
safety I've burned things up I've blown
things up on purpose not because I like
explosions but I see yeah there was one
that that one time we won't talk about
that I wanted to see what this can
handle so i' I've detonated units like
that while I've been holding them and
they go and they're fine so that's why I
like this CPVC you can't put enough
hydrogen in here with your stainless
steel plates in order to really damage
it um this is an off-the-shelf uh CPVC
lid they're about 100 bucks I just
happen to have one laying around so you
can do many things you can put two of
these on the
ends and bolt them together you can you
could drop this unit down into a 5
gallon bucket don't really recommend it
but you could drop that down into a 5
gallon bucket and hook up a hose off of
it it doesn't really matter um I'm a
huge fan of safety so I like the the the
indestructible nature of this
um do you have the dimensions on these
uh diameters just for people who want to
a recipe this is an 8 in nominal CPVC
pipe that means that um it's about 8 and
1/2 on the outside and 7 and
3/4 or uh excuse me uh just under eight
on the inside what's that 7 7 say so8
thank you do you have to worry about the
cutting getting rid of any magnetism or
whatever that might build up stcity are
talking about the metal
plates um in the metal plates what you
see here are sheared stainless steel
plates and we don't really I haven't had
to deal with magnetism issues like you
would with a conventional Joe cell if
you're doing con uh concentric stainless
steel tubes you do have to deal with
magnetism issues which is very easy to
to uh just simply use a torch heat them
up and take out the magnetism but with
stainless steel plates uh just sheare
them don't don't laser cut them if you
laser cut them uh it's a little more
expensive than shearing if you can find
a Shear it's a it's a good way to go I
have lots of stainless steel plates if
people want to buy them pretty cheap too
I have lots of 6x6 plates so um you just
stack them together and hold uh and hold
them apart with spacers and then I've
got a clamp piece of plastic that I had
laying around the shop and just clamp it
together soy simple since this is going
to be cut into several segments let's go
ahead and mention your domain name um
alchemical hydrogen. comom and ancient
tech.com and Tech is TE K TK thank you
yes ancient tech oh and the other thing
that I used to hold this on is
a uh is um Plumbing goop that you can
find from from uh at Home Depot both of
them uh so you put put Plumbing goop
down okay and then you form your form
your gask and it's actually round
completely round when you start here
where it overlaps right here and you get
a good seal where it overlaps very good
yeah very good seal usually I'll I'll
I'll fold it over the top that got moved
a little bit and see it's still sealed
anyway so that's why I love this stuff
and then I just use a stainless steel
plate that I clamp down on top um this
has some grooves in it to guide the uh
to guide the Teflon where I want it to
go as you can see the grooves All In
there as well just to just to seal it up
very well um on that system machined
here yes it's uh machined out I I cut it
actually it was cut for one of those and
I just said you know what I'll just
throw it on here what kind of material
is this this is uh 304 stainless since
this isn't being used as an electrolysis
section or excuse me in the electrolysis
section you can use 304 versus 316 and
it's about a third the or 2/3 the price
what's that no no your plates are 316
right my plates are 316 right yes my
plates are
316 um so let me have let me ask you a
question uh if you take what neutral of
each cell the voltage of the cell will
go up right how you came with 16 bolts
and four neutrals for each L um out of
experimenting trying
TR yeah experimenting to find the find
the best voltage to drop this out so if
I put two three three neutrals only it
will generate more more heat it will
generate more heat but but you've got a
lot of you're putting a lot of power in
there um so but what about
elements um I don't know we're we're
still in the experimental phase here
okay this this is this this um system
people have been probably transmuting
elements more than they realize but this
system I've only been working with for
like four months so this is um so so
actually transmuting elements and seeing
seeing all the ramifications there it's
wide open right now so I and I encourage
people to experiment I encourage them
people to um build these devices maybe
get some maybe get some gold and
platinum from ancient Tech and uh and
and seat it and start playing with it um
people actually somebody asked me in the
elevator about using seawat and like the
gentleman did in the experiment or in
their uh in their work to that they they
uh electroly the Great Salt Lake water
and they get a lot of gold out from it
um in I would be very careful with that
because you're producing a lot of
chlorine gas uh very very dangerous
stuff you definitely don't want to be
running that into your uh into an engine
you want to be washing that out so I'd
be very careful using uh seawater but
Spring Water um ormis water if anybody's
familiar with ormis uh distilled
distilled water if you use if you're
going to spike it if you're going to put
some gold in there if you're going to
put some Platinum aridium something like
that is this purely scientific in other
words whatever elements are in the water
are going to be multiplied or is there
some intention so that human thought and
intention and uh you know you can create
or diminish depending on intentionality
or is it completely scientific that is a
very good question um I haven't seen
intention be involved in this yet but
it's still fairly young field so we
might see more of that in the future so
intention uh I
would I do a little prayer meditation
each day I do I get up every morning
with the sun and do uh or before the sun
and do some uh do some prayer and
meditation and do some sungazing and I
put the intention into the day that that
the highest and best will that is is
going to happen highest and best is not
always what we want okay highest the
best is is what the universe has in
store for us it's it's the path that God
has for us you know however you want to
put it the highest and best may not be
what we want but it's but um it doesn't
mean it always happens okay but uh so I
try and hold that intentional day and I
try to um it's difficult to work
actually in my shop with a bad attitude
and and such you know based off of you
know our experience with that you've
actually talked about before with uh
with your your thoughts and your
emotions and our aeic energy devices so
um maybe as we experiment more we'll see
you know maybe meditation is the best
way to go I mean I I've seen some
amazing things done by people all
praying and meditating in unison around
a bowl of water and
manifesting reality outside of
themselves so really amazing stuff so
maybe we'll see more of that as more
people work on this it's like it's like
uh the the microchip manufacturers they
discovered that uh they discovered or
the computer manufacturers discovered
that computers work faster when the
person operating them is in the good
mood so instead of encouraging everybody
to be in a good mood they started foring
on ways to Shield their
microprocessors from emotions okay seems
kind of counterproductive to me because
hey what if we all got in a really
really good space and we can create
supercomputers hey what an interesting
idea so and I believe anyway that's
esoteric we need to go there okay we've
talked about materials is there any
reason to explain materials this is my
base this is just a base that I use to
hold this up off of the uh it could be
anything basically it could be anything
basically um as a matter of fact I had
originally envisioned this thing flipped
upside down and I wanted to call it my
little R2
unit yes Veron uhhuh when you put
materials in there yes what's the
maximum amount of increase that you've
seen when you put in like one part of
gold that you would see maybe you
mentioned earli 15 16 times or how high
do you think that could go to um I don't
know yet uh we've seen at least 13 times
multiplication uh as soon as we get a we
know that the elements are being
multiplied and because we've measured it
with certain detection devices we take
it away we still got the same amount
that we started with Excuse me and more
are over here and we can we can detect
the the uh the elements that are over
here but we don't know exactly how much
so we've seen we've seen at least 13
times have you tried to put it in
circulation recirculation put it back in
yeah recirculate um no I have not yet we
and and that's definitely on the list of
things to do is it conceivable that you
could have a continuous flowing of your
sub of the things that you're making you
you seed it with gold for example and
then you run it and it and you pull it
off at a certain rate
and you just keep pulling it off and
it's being created from the hydrogen
oxygen gas and the alchemical process
well that's essentially what we're
seeing here uh you can you pull it off
you pull it off over here isn't that an
infinite scenario not a 13-fold
well I guess I I I see what you're
saying um it would be infinite if you
just let it keep on going okay um I do
turn this off I do you know the sun goes
down and I and it and it uh everything
condenses and I take it apart every once
in a while so I don't know the exact
numbers yet and you know as we quantify
this we're in the we're in the we're in
the advanced theoretical stage here now
we need to quantify the numbers we need
to start figuring out exactly what's
happening here so we can get ratios of
hydrogen oxygen elements generated um so
and there's a lot of experimentation to
be done this is fairly new this is just
4 months
four or five months old this particular
deal we seen a duplication of Organics
you know versus inorganics in
there
um that is a very interesting question
and I can't answer it without um telling
a really different story so I'm going to
have to pass on that one I apologize so
the short answer is yes what's up the
short answer is yes
probably yeah okay anybody familiar with
Lee
Scallan yeah he wrote an interesting
little pamplet it was called um animal
vegetable and mineral life and everybody
thinks it's a typo because it's animal
life and vegetable life and then we got
minerals but then I started getting
really deep into
Alchemy let me let me demystify Alchemy
really quick Alchemy is the study of
finding the seed of life of something
anything whether it be an element or a
mineral whether it be gold or platinum
or whatever Alchemy is discovering the
seed of life of something finding the
soil in which it's going to grow and
putting them together and cultivating
them so whether that means I'm going to
find the seed of life of gold and put it
together in the soil that it's going to
grow in let's say 10 and then
cultivating and letting it grow with
heat and multiplying my gold that's
that's one element of alchemy where
that's an idea in a fertile mind and
putting it into and and cultivating it
with proper thoughts proper energy and
directed action and creating a new
reality that's
Alchemy um so what Lee Scallan was
talking about is saying we're going to
find the seed of life of of a mineral
we're going to find what it grows in and
that's what the pamphlet is about he was
talking about magnetic fields and making
it grow so uh and that pamphlet was all
about about alchemy but most people
think it's just kind of the ramblings of
a of a very eccentric person so um the
short answer is yes the short answer is
we have seen
organic life grow in here how that is
measured is a little
bit harder to quantify so that's that's
the that's uh my reticence there have we
gone through all the materials and the
the um specs on the design are we ready
to talk about let me just show real
quick here this is a a very I like this
way of putting power into it this is a
bolt or excuse me this is a uh a pipe
threaded fitting through the wall of the
of the vessel and I put a bolt in here a
stainless steel bolt and welded it on
the end so that I get a completely
sealed uh completely sealed threaded um
threaded insert with that can put
electricity in and come out on the
inside so that's that's something that's
really important I struggled for a very
long time to figure out how to put an
electrode through with washers and and
such that aren't going to break down
over time and that are not going to not
going to suffer from the expansion and
contraction as this thing heats up and
cools off this is the best system that I
found to do it um the only the only
other system is to use that I like is to
use this as an electrode which I do on
the other uh which I I do on the other
on the other machines but this is a uh
this is a little bit different way to do
it so I like this way you put a bolt
through and you weld it on and then
thread that in place and then you've got
a contact inside that you can run your
uh run your electricity off of and so
this is just a regular connection here
just a nut this is a this is a stainless
steel bolt that's run through and I just
put on the uh put on the wires with with
two bolts and tighten them down together
the reason why I put this glue in place
there is because I have
experienced over time these these bolts
these nuts that have been uh threaded
onto the bolt over time as they heat up
and cool off they can loosen up and then
you get a little tiny little tiny spark
in there and you got hydrogen right here
little tiny spark from the uh from the
contacts and boom so that's why I put
the the uh the glue in place there so
that that can't wiggle loose and uh and
Spark what kind of glue uh that's once
again the uh the Plumbing
goop that's great stuff I use tubes and
tubes of that and that's what is called
commercially Plumbing goop yes that's
what it's called okay same thing to it's
in the pl it's in the purple it's in the
purple uh the purple tube what's that
yeah you can't use it for sealing
completely you cannot use it to just
seal the lid in place I've tried that
doesn't work you have to use the Teflon
you have to use something to something
to hold it pressurized like this bolt it
together pressure holding it it together
um you cannot just use a solvent to hold
it unless you're using like like here
this is just solvent it on the pipe onto
the uh onto the lid or the cap rather uh
but that's uh 4 in of solvent and it's
it's really strong so that's that that's
good but an inch of uh solvent or an
inch or excuse me half an inch of
solvent or half an inch of glue won't
hold things together you have to seal it
with h seal it with compression what
about these fittings right here these
are um conventional uh
CPVC fittings you buy them at at Walmart
or Home Depot with Teflon fittings I use
I use teflon regular Teflon pipe tape to
thread that in place um and they're they
have a maximum their maximum heat is
about
180° but if you're running 180° here
something's wrong so you don't want to
go that high what about the fitting on
the bottom the fitting on the bottom is
just the same deal it's just gone out
sideways any reasons for the diameter
that you're using there is looks like
it's about a qu inch I half almost half
inch yeah half inch I think these are uh
I think it's /4 in
npt um it's just stuff I had laying
around okay I could I could use a
smaller um I I'll dispel it it's not
really a myth but it's a it's a
conception that says you need huge pipe
or excuse me huge diameters uh to run
your gas through you can run 20 l a
minute through a uh through a/4 inch
pipe
and I haven't seen any significant drop
or I haven't seen any significant
difference between using a large pipe or
small pipe to run your hydrogen through
so I don't I don't think you need a huge
pipe in the beginning I was using 1 inch
diameter 1inch diameter hose to run my
hydrogen to the engines and such because
I thought that I needed to then I
started doing some experiments because
that's you know kind of what I was told
so I started doing some experiments and
I proved out that I didn't need to I
could use a qu or 3/8 in uh diam hose
like you see here and uh do it just fine
so you have your own spect what's that
do you have your own Spectra I have a
friend who developed a detection
technology that is um that is uh without
par okay it is amazing technology um he
has he can scan the moon okay uh he has
revolutionized
um
uh shipwreck uh shipwreck discoveries
and get on the get on the boat tune in
for whatever he's looking for whether it
be gold or or jewels from a Spanish
gallion or something like that and they
can drive their boat to it send divers
down and their right on every time so
and it's a beautiful little detection
technology this a little device about
yay big and they can detect they can
detect oh they detected thorium and c
and cesium Landing in the mountains of
Utah from Fukushima so yeah that was
kind of freaky box with the uh angle of
the divining rods go with um I don't
think it uses divining rods anymore F
jural no okay so basically dialing any
element on the periodic chart any
element on the planet he he gave it to
uh gave it to the uh the police
department in Salt Lake City they dial
in the chemical compound of
methamphetamine drive to a meth laab so
they he sent two of them to Iraq uh
they're not quite as user friendly as
the military would like to have so uh
they they they're not asking for more
but basically guys that were well
trained on them and and and we were very
good with using them could tell from a
distance of five miles where an
improvised explosive device was located
and they could tell the guys you're
going go forward 300 yards and you're
going to go to your right and you'll
find it they're buried 2 feet
underground that type of thing so the
technology is
without yeah it's amazing stuff it's
like having a tricorder from Star Trek
okay like you know yeah I I met somebody
down in the Mount Pleasant Utah area
who's passed away now who developed a
technology like that not
Robert was it Robert no I can't remember
his name right um it's in my address
book he passed away about two years ago
oh no yeah okay but anyway should we
talk now about um the we've talked about
assembly and what's involved what about
um operation how to run it um operating
these is fairly simple you want to put
uh of course you put voltage in at some
point
now what I believe from the experiments
and the and the things that I've seen so
far what I believe is that a puls
frequency uh device will drop out the
elements that are there a DC device will
multip the the elements that are that
you seated with I could be completely
wrong on this and I'm challenging people
to try and figure out you know the
nature of this I mean here we are nicoa
Tesla we're going to throw the AC motor
out there and how many people can find
new applications for it um here we are
we've got a hydrogen element dropper
outer
multiplier and go out and find out the
ramifications about it because this is
brand new and anyone can do it I mean as
you can see it's not that it's not
difficult um you put voltage across and
I just use I just use uh usually I use
solar panel sometimes I'll hook it up to
my uh my uh DC uh DC power supply I'll
plug DC power into here so I can let it
run for for a week straight instead of
you know on and off every day and you
get the same result it doesn't care
where the DC is coming from not care um
it's just the solar panels free so you
put it on there and the the reason I
asked that is because we might think
it's all the same by our measurement
detection but there could be other
things going on that we're not aware of
uh radiant energy flows over the wires
not through them for example that's
right if you want something to flow you
call a plumber not an electrician what
energy flows around it not through it
you're absolutely right um we have
actually discovered a distinct
difference between a solar panel
voltage and a lead acid battery voltage
and a lithium ion
voltage don't ask me to describe it it's
it it it's uh it's a little bit outside
of uh you know where I'm comfortable
talking about because it moves into the
marriage of esoteric energies and uh and
science so it's very interesting yeah
very basic pro and con against which
one um I am not a fan of lithium
ion uh I I do not like it I can go into
the environmental impacts of it you can
you you are less environment you are
less impacting the environment by
driving a Hummer than you are by driving
a Prius okay because of the lithium ion
and the uh and the uh the environmental
impact of making the batteries and
disposing of the batteries and disposing
of the batteries thank you yes why is
supposed to doable what's that you're
supposed to be recyclable yes but just
making them is incredibly harmful the
mining of them mining of it the uh the
manufacturing process the whole thing
but but if you're replicating the
minerals the lithium and the ion using
this then what well then then we're
looking at a complete we have the
ability now to uh to mine the ocean we
have the ability now to manufacture the
elements that we need um all we need is
water and energy and a seed so the seed
of life finding where it will grow and
encouraging it to do so um so perhaps
then things things will change but we
don't like the lithium ion there is a uh
there's aluminum in lithium ion battery
systems um this is going to get really
esoteric so if you guys don't like it on
the video go ahead and fast forward now
but there was a woman making the rounds
in The Prophecy Club about 20 years ago
that could kill rats using carbon
dioxide gas kill she demonstrated this
many times on stage she could kill rats
using carbon dioxide gas lay her hands
over them and bring them back to life
many people witnessed this she just
blessed them and brought them back to
life there's one criteria there could
not be any aluminum within 100 fet of
where she was working if there was she
couldn't bring them back to life one
time they thought they found all the
aluminum in the area that she was uh
demonstrating this and she was praying
and they weren't coming back to life and
she was praying and and blessing them
and and they found one little strip of
aluminum on a label underneath a table
and she grabbed the rats ran out into
the field knelt down and prayed over
them and they all came back to life so
I'm not a fan of
aluminum now I'm not that crazy I'm not
that I'm not crazy but that intense
about it because hey I'm not bringing
rats back to life but um aluminum when I
did my research into the Bible Code uh
aluminum one was one of the few metals
that had
absolute injunctions against
using um there there were a couple of
the noble medals too actually osmium was
really bad in the which one I want to
say it wasn't I want to say ruthenium
but I'm not certain uh but when I
studied that what's up well go ahead I
was just going to ask what would be an
aluminum substitute since you're using
aluminum in this setting I'm not using
any aren't you oh I'm sorry
sing what's up what do they put in our
water now fluoride where you get fluide
aluminum yeah fluoride uh fluoride is a
toxic uh is a toxic industrial byproduct
and the men that handle the fluoride
barrels are wearing full Hazmat gear
until they pour it into the the pipe
that feeds the city and then
everything's
fine fluoride is also how the Germans
how a handful of Germans soldiers maybe
10 or 13 German soldiers could keep a
thousand uh people in a prison camp
completely calm and relaxed and just
ushered them towards the gas Chambers
because they've been giving them so much
fluoride they the people couldn't you
know rise up so so back to I'm going to
step off the pedestal the soap box now
the DC power DC power going in here any
type you want to play with it doesn't
matter solar panels positive which is
negative um in this condition no it
doesn't I set this up to be positive and
this up to be negative and I've got my
negative pole in the center and my
positive on the edges and that's
all to go one way or the other it only
matters if you're going to be in in an
area where you could brush up where
where the edge of your machine could
brush up against a ground so let's say
you were building something like this
and you're putting it into a car um
you'd want to position your positive and
your negative so that it didn't uh so it
couldn't brush so that your positive
could not brush up against the frame of
your vehicle so that's the only that's
the only criteria but that's more of a
uh installation concern rather than a
design concern so um I I like this way
it's personal preference
but I like how this generates gas there
are subtle differences and but that
takes that takes like the a year of
working with the gas to to start see the
subtle differences and different people
resonate with different uh setups so
this is the way I like is there any um
entrainment or not that's not the word
I'm looking for conditioning
conditioning involved in this not
involved with this uh there's
conditioning with this and this is a
conditioning process and I can describe
that real quick um conditioning the
plates in a system like
this you power it with a little bit over
current it's a little bit uh a little
bit more energy than you would normally
power and you cannot power it with pulse
DC but you condition the plates uh by
running them with um with a whole lot of
sodium hydroxide and some gold and uh
some elect some of my electric water and
you you let the water run you let the
water boil away you don't replenish it
you let it all run out what that does is
it puts a nice layer of you can't see it
on these but it puts a nice conditioning
layer on the plate and then you do it
again layer of layer of catalyst put a
nice conditioned layer of catalyst
essentially what you're doing is you're
you're uh conditioning the first first
uh molecule the first atoms of the uh of
each plate you're conditioning them with
a with a material that's going to
encourage the production of hydrogen
it's going to take it to the point of
separation and then your electricity
pushes it over so that's that's what
we're going on here I know that your
system works a little little bit differ
us um that's what that's how you
condition this that's the that's a
secret okay secret boy I'm no good at
actually really good you actually sand
the place first right what's up you sand
the plates first do you sand the plates
I do sand the plates actually I don't
sand the plates anymore let me show you
what I do real quick that's kind of like
anod aluminum you're creating a hard
surface or a different surface yeah uh
let me tell real quick here what I just
described with letting the water run out
uh letting the water run out during the
conditioning process instead of instead
of replenishing it and keeping it full
that is something that took me a lot of
years to learn because I I I would
condition it take me it take me a week
to to properly condition a plate the the
protocols are on uh actually they're on
Pez wikii right now in in a lot of Bob
boices work so
um but when I when I learned that if you
let it let let the water level drop over
as as it's uh as it's running and then
when you fill it back up it's going to
Condition it's going to run even better
but that's only with that's only with my
gold Catalyst that's not with regular
sodium hydroxide follow the normal
conditioning procedures that Bob laid
out with sodium hydroxide and and you'll
be you'll be fine but anyway um what I
do now instead of
sanding because I've been working in
production levels um I have to I have to
find the fastest way to do this so I was
working when I was doing these I was
running about 3 minutes of proper
sanding and conditioning or proper
sanding and prepping of each plate okay
and that was just way too slow when
you're doing an uh 120 plate system or
something like that just takes way too
long so what I actually found was that
if I took a wire brush I don't know if
you can see that on the camera yeah you
can took a wire brush on my shows better
on the camera than it does really oh
nice I took a wire brush on my drill
motor and
just and what's interesting is this is
uh like it looks very similar to the
tree of or the Flower of Life diagrams
they found in Egypt so I really like
this way of uh conditioning the plates
and I do that to all my plates I
just and I can do a plate in about 20 30
seconds completely completely uh
scratched or prepped for uh for the box
so and then I just liked it I just like
the I like the pattern so much I did all
my ends with it too so anyway uh I think
you can you can even see it on that one
there yeah too just for Aesthetics one
more question on that yes I've asked you
before I didn't understand okay does
that go in water or this is not water
like it is this is what we call a dry
cell the water is only
inside and inside the uh inside the
circle okay so you see the circle here
right I remember now so we're going to
put water in here there's little holes
drilled in the bottom of the plates and
that's what communicates the water to
the center and then the hydrogen is
generated comes out the holes in the top
and escapes there so this is what we
call a dry cell when you say hydrogen
you're talking Hydrox hogen and oxygen
excuse me hydroxy um Brown's gas
whatever you want to call it there's
this there's a there's a conflict
between the Brownian and the rodians
and they they're saying No it should be
called Brown's gas no it should be
called Road's gas no it should be called
there super gas now and
whatnot roads pioneered the work started
it out much as much as you see me doing
this here round uh excuse me uh Brown
took the work and Quantified it there is
I there's actually things that I can't
say about Brown and his work with the
hydrogen because it's not mine to give
away and some somebody else fed it to me
under under confidentiality but let me
just say that what I talked about in my
lecture about water about the different
parts of water is so important for
proper Browns gas uh research um that
there are different parts of water if
you distill a court if you distill a
gallon jug into Four Courts every Court
will have its own characteristics and
you want to use certain courts you
actually want to use the first two
quarts that come off in the last two for
an alch or what we call
fixed um you don't want to use the last
two quarts you want to use the first two
quarts use the last two quarts for
watering your plants or something to
give a plug it you say two gallons of
water you distill it from a you get it
from a nice stream and distill it what
do you mean by distill it okay before we
answer that question pull it off can you
pause for a second please um just to
give a plug for where people can get
those um DVDs of your presentation go to
Tesla
techinfo and those will be available
shortly where you can purchase a DVD of
your presentation and I would recommend
doing it was a fascinating presentation
you gave yesterday I'm really excited
because this is the first time in three
years that they've actually got a copy
of my
presentation for the last uh it was yeah
it was the last three years somehow the
the copy of my of my lecture was
destroyed um the sound was completely
garbled it was unintelligible or the uh
or or the video just didn't show up it I
I find that very ironic very interesting
so they' already produced it this one
they know as a matter of fact they set
up a special camera in there was
completely independent of everything
else recording it just to make certain
that they that everything worked out
right okay your your question is uh how
do you distill water you can distill
water you can get a there's a stainless
steel distill well plastic shell on the
outside stainless steel on the inside
you can distill water um any type of
water but if you distill reverse osmosis
water it'll be much cleaner on your uh
on your distiller unit so you just pour
the water in it distills off and like I
said um for Brown's gas work you want to
take the first two quarts that come off
okay Brown had a little bit different
way of separating his water which like I
said I can't talk about it because I I
have to honor my you know my silence no
I have to honor my uh you know the the
confidentiality so um anyway uh so the
first two quarts of water what you want
to use in in in in all these systems the
other quarts you want to add to your uh
add to your Gardens or or water your
plants with or because they're what an
alchemist would call fixed they're
harder to separate the first two are
very volatile and you they are they're
much more tuned to what we have here so
okay that said um and so you're using
the first two um quarts coming from the
distiller to run in this process yes
uhhuh yeah um and so you actually for
for this process you could throw in
spring water and that's good I mean you
would think well you're going to use the
first two but what you're saying is
don't use the third fourth and fifth in
your in your batch that goes on the
garden that's right only use the first
two and if you want to make six
quarts you know you're going to have to
do this three times to get the first two
quarts um off of each process that's
right that's right um and that's that
was one of the things that really
launched some of my hydrogen work when I
when I realized that the water itself
that I was using was was very important
not all distilled Waters created equal
so would you say that this alchemical
process you've discovered is that that's
a crucial um component or or uh
something that is a make or break this
this will work without it okay I mean
all hydr will work without it you can
just use distilled water you just use
whatever your uh whatever you want to in
this one you can throw in Spring Water
you can throw in salt salt uh ocean
water if you're if you're really uh
adventurous um but what I found to make
really good gas and to have really
Dynamic and Powerful effects if you use
the the the first two of water um the
first two uh sections of water you will
find a more uh you'll find a more
powerful gas you'll find it separates
more easily that type of thing so it's a
preference not a requirement um someday
it may be a preference because I'll tell
you what how many people are uh or me
not somay it may be a requirement not a
preference because how many people are
remediating uh nuclear waste like brown
did is there anybody
people have tried it and they can't do
it but if you use this other system you
can really yeah I lost lost that because
Brown did not talk about where he was
getting his water okay Brown did not
talk about the type of water he was
using that was his secret so let's get
back into the procedure of us of running
this thing MH we've talked about the
preparation of the water we talked about
the hooking up of the DC um what are the
considerations is there a pump involved
in running um voltages you want to run
if you set it up the way I've done it
you run uh you run a a 12vt solar panel
and no no panels are 12 volts they're
actually like eight or 16 and that's
fine just hook up the solar panel run it
to it um if you're running this like
this on over here you're going to uh
you're going to daisy chain your solar
panels together and generate 120 volts
and put it into it but for this one a
12vt this design I've created here a
12vt solar panel um not really concerned
about the amperage it'll take as much as
it wants and and uh you won't overload
your panel um and and just have at it so
12 volts or or 18 volts or whatever it's
called if you don't get up to 20 volts
because that's way or 20 24 excuse me a
24volt panel uh just stick with the
regular panels that you can use to
charge batteries um an RV solar panel uh
or a couple of them work together that's
fine
so or a DC power supply a lot of lot of
generators have DC power supplies now
you just hook up click click from the
from the uh generator and the way you go
now a lay person how much are you
filling this all the way to the top with
water well how are you telling how part
it see my see my uh little line there
I'm not filling it all the way up I'm
not filling it up to these
electrodes um basically I just measured
how much water was going to fill in here
I figured about a gallon in half and a
gallon and a half it's a little bit High
uh next time I'll use about a gallon and
a quar um so that the water is below the
plates but it doesn't really matter as
long as you're not filling it all the
way up and uh you know allowing this
electrode to to interact with that
electrode because then you're going to
lose a lot of your power here and you
want to focus your power
here um now what about how do you
maintain the level if because aren't
aren't you having is there a continuous
flow of through here or is it a batch
process if you when you hook it up to
the the reservoir over here you can
actually see the level that you're at
okay when I've got it like this I just
know that I'm going to run it for you
know um I'm just going to pour in a
gallon and a half and let it go but if
you have a reservoir over here you can
actually raise the raise and lower the
reservoir and you'll see the the line of
the water and you just adjust as uhjust
as you see yeah you really want the
water to be right about the the top of
the plates maybe just a little bit lower
and that that's fine so with the
reservoir makes it very
easy so that's a good thing so give us a
step process number one you put the
water number two you put the lid on is
okay number one you take your water
whatever your water you're going to use
whether it's going to be spring water if
you're going to if you're going to uh be
brave and try uh salt uh Salt Lake water
or ocean water your water or or My Water
uh my elements mix that all up together
um in a system like this you're looking
at about a gallon and a half maybe a
gallon and a/ qu uh like I said you can
put this in a 5 gallon bucket and then
that's really easy okay my plates are
sitting about 6 in off the bottom I know
that I'm going to put in 2 and 1 half
gallons okay but measure out your water
find out exactly how much you want pour
that in there and then uh actually you
want to seal this first because you can
add your water here so you want to seal
this up because this is not going to
seal properly if it gets wet and when
you're working around and trying to get
all these bolts that's why actually
they're all unequal so so that it's
easier to put them on it's like okay
this one and then that one and that one
and and then you just suck them down um
how much time do you have to work with
with that um plumber's
[Music]
um uh how long does it set up you want
you want to be sealing it up within
about uh within less than 10 minutes
okay I like I like to give it about 5
minutes on on a cool day I'll I'll uh I
won't worry about it too much but on a
hot day I want it sealed up within 5
minutes okay so and that includes uh
putting the nuts on yep well you you you
put it in place and then you just uh
start tightening down the nuts depending
on on your mechanism of ceiling uh I
actually toyed with the idea of putting
a clamp on there clamping it down and
then tightening down the nuts and that
works too but
um you you put it in place and that's
the first stage and then you tighten
down your nuts and you want all that
done within within 10 minutes okay and
then um let's talk about filling up the
reservoir um since we don't have the
reservoir to demonstrate here can you
can we use something just as a visual
okay so we're here theose was going to
go to the bottom and this hose would go
to the top let's for M for the actually
the earlier portion where describing the
components let's describe the reservoir
what okay actually this is this is the
resir I should have thought that this is
the reservoir right
here so as you can see the
reservoir is actually higher than the
highest level of this hydrogen device
and there's different ways to play with
this and I don't want to go into the
minute of that because it's really comes
down to personal preference but as you
can see filling up this device will
bring you to right about here okay okay
and so what and so you can actually see
how much water you have in your hydrogen
device by the level in your Reservoir
okay and so you open that up pour it in
fill it up to there it's equalizes it
drops down you fill it up again and and
you're you're fine any preferences on
size of reservoir no it's it's totally
personal preference these things are
eight bucks a piece so I've said hey
can't argue with that I'm just gonna
um buy them and put them in place it's
$8 so they're fairly pretty cheap and uh
not not difficult to use and using the
same reservoir on this system over here
yep same deal okay cuz I had a lot of
them laying around okay this is a safety
bubbler you're not going to be running
an engine off of this thing well maybe
you are if you're running an engine off
this thing you want to run it through a
safety bubbler right let's let's stick
with this scenario of doing let's now
pretend like this is your Reser
for demonstration purposes so we're
going to run this bottom hose to the
bottom of this Reservoir run the top
hose to the top of this Reservoir and
we're going to look and see where the
level of our plates are compared to uh
where where it corresponds to on this uh
on this Reservoir okay and so we're
going to fill up the reservoir to the
level that we that is indicated by where
the plates are so you're pouring the
water into the reservoir when yes you're
pouring the water into the
reservoir and you pour pour the water
down into the reservoir and it will this
will equalize pretty quickly so
basically as fast as you can pour it in
it's going to flow in there and equalize
and when you reach the proper level
that's where you stop you you can play
around with it but you prob might want
to put a mar on the outside of this just
to be sure right exactly and then also
you're going to want to have some way to
fasten your Reservoir in relation to the
main tank so that they're not moving
back and forth and right on like on my
uh in my video present I had a picture
of my entire safety setup on the wall M
and part of that was the reservoir yeah
and I feed this unit with that same
Reservoir that I feed all my other
hydrogen units so um they're all Daisy
chained together so that's it's pretty
simple okay um so that's uh that's the
setup and I'm assuming that people are
just going to let this uh let this
hydrogen boil off into the air if you're
inside you want to run a hose to the
outside if you are letting to sit
outside you're fine um you can you can
bubble it off through a through a a
safety bubbl or something run it to a
generator whatever your whatever your
preference is it doesn't really matter
what if you're um in the alchemical
process you're experimenting and you've
got some kind of a toxic um substance
that you're replicating then you would
probably are you going to have any of
that coming out inde what you want is a
uh if you're playing with that stuff
it's going to be pretty advanced but if
you're playing with that stuff you want
to have multiple washes of water now the
the other the other uh this this um this
container right here is the safety
bubbler and the wash okay and what
happens is the the the gas bubbles
through there and any particulates any
any uh residual from the machine is
going to collect in that uh in the
second
bubbler and what you want if you're
playing with toxic stuff you want
multiple stages of those so by the time
you get down here your gas is completely
clean and you want them to be tall too I
use uh I use a harell uh clear PVC pipes
put caps on the end and bubble gas
through it because I can actually see
I'm a very visual person I can actually
see the bubbles and I can see the gas
escaping I saw a
$50,000 hydrogen prototype destroyed in
10 minutes because he had no visual
feedback okay he relied entirely upon
computer gizmos and gadgets to tell him
what was going on and one of them failed
it was like a China Syndrome a 25 cent
piece failed and a $50,000 prototype was
destroyed after 10 minutes I'm a very
big fan of visual feedback one bubbler
would have told him that something was
wrong but he thought but he was relying
on a computer so visual feedback on top
of that and as I mentioned in my lecture
if you got a long column of water and
you're bubbling hydrogen through it have
fun with it put a rodent coil around it
see what happens we're dealing with a
with a practically an electrolytic gas
here yes try energizing it with uh with
high frequency energies and such um
there's one guy that was playing with
this back in the 60s and he would had a
little separator as the most inefficient
thing on the face of the planet but then
he'd run it between two 8 in plates very
similar to my Lids there he ran it
between two 8 in plates that were
separated about 2 in apart that would
had a high voltage Corona in the center
of it not enough to not enough spark to
ignite it but enough but enough energy
to turn that hydrogen gas into detarium
and he was running his car on so play
with columns shine lasers Through It
Shine uh ultraviolet lasers through it
do different stuff like that and you'll
start to see the quality of gas change
you start to see the manifestation I um
I swear someday we're going to see
somebody running a torch and they're
going to start depositing gold on a
piece of Steel and that'll be really
cool so anyway um that's the setup if
you're working with experiment working
with elements like that you want to have
multiple stages just to make certain
that whatever you escape off into the
air or what if you bleed off into the
air is going to be is going to be clean
what about the uh as you're running this
uh are you expecting the water level to
to drop and it it's not going to drop
super fast since we're only producing
like I said this one's going 20 lers an
hour there's your expansion ratio is at
least 1,800 to
one so 1,800 L is going to take a little
while to go through and that's burning
through one gallon of water but if
you're bleeding it off and taking your
minerals out that you're that you're um
that you're uh multiplying then you just
you know keep on adding water in
proportion to the minerals or the water
that you've taken out let's talk about
harvesting minerals um and you've got
the setup where you've got the the uh
Reservoir and where where are the
minerals showing up and how do you Minal
are showing up the minerals are showing
up in the water that comes out of here
and collects in your
Reservoir um and what you're going to do
there's a number of different ways to to
work with that uh I would suggest
everybody get uh the book recovery and
process of precious metals by Bill aan
because that is the intive work excuse
me on how to recover elements from any
any situation whether it be an ore or a
uh or a deposit or whatever you're
working with um lot of from an oil well
what's that R from ran from an oil well
oh boy howy you missed it yesterday uh I
talked about my oil well experience
there I didn't I didn't get back in time
I didn't get down in time to hear about
it but we
we we we processed water from
three uh oil wells stripper Wells uhhuh
uh the brine was considered so strong
that it was hazardous waste and it had
to be diluted before it could be
reinjected really and the wells produced
maybe two barrels a week mhm and 98
barrels
of Brian did you ever do an analys
analysis on the uh on the Brian I got uh
two I was able to smelt uh out of the we
did De process okay uh and the waste the
precipitate we had we worked with and uh
I got 8 O of silver out of 50
gallons wow that's good stuff I love it
that's fantastic I may bring 10 gallons
down to you okay excellent sounds like a
blast yeah but the same thing it's it's
a guy in Denver that's uh the leading
gold smelter here in you have to find a
place to you have to find a place to
process it exactly did you use this
process to precipitate out and drop out
the the oh yeah we we we ran it uh we
were pulling 20 amps we had an outdoor
tank which we had to stuff in and the
plates in and and it was a cone shaped
tank so we collect the precipitant out
afterwards and we would run it until the
volage went to zip because the salts
were all gone ah like you say we
collected the precipitate there you go
afterwards and processed the precipitant
after that and um how much
go well in this particular there was
very little gold and there was some
Platinum but very little but it was
mostly silver in this particular
um going going back we got another
affirmation of what's going on here yeah
well that's that's the dropping out
that's not the multiplying but that's
the dropping out so there there we go
yeah exactly we're actually part part of
this Al you missed the first part is
actually about multiplication of
elements too yes which is which with the
hydrogen oxygen and the energy is is
happening quite abundantly I'd like to
talk to you more about AB that's what we
were we were doing okay we we actually
had some seed
silver
ah I see so here's another this a smart
man he's working with silver not that
stupid yellow
metal exactly uhhuh and uh there you go
uh there wasn't any trouble we could
send the silver off to there you go and
get it we wound up with nuggets that
were 82% silver and the rest of it
Canadians just gave us back pure silver
bars
nice that's excellent Al thank you and
you don't mind us including that in our
YouTube video
here I see no reason why not okay no all
right it's
interesting so back to this process here
could you walk through um kind of
visually walk us through the process of
doing a scenario where let's you know
putting some kind of mineral in you want
to replicate it beginning to end kind of
just step by step so we're going to seal
up our device completely we're going to
put the lid on and we're going to seal
it down completely with our with our
o-ring um and that's only important if
you're actually capturing your hydrogen
and running it I mean like I said you
can have this in a 5 gallon bucket but
I'm all about multi-purposes I'm all
about uh finding different ways and so
if we're boiling hydrogen off you know
there's no purpose to to that unless
we're using it and like I said this is
what I'll I'll heat my shop with this
year during this during the winter um we
seal it together we put everything
putting put everything together we prep
our solution in a in a in a gallon or
two gallons of water okay we either use
our our high concentration Spring Water
our salt water if for brave we use our
um our our mineral water electric water
whatever you want to concentrate you you
prepare that over here and you pour that
into into your Reservoir okay your
Reservoir which is sitting you know yay
yay high which is marked on the side to
show where you want to uh where you want
to fill it up to you pour it in there
and the and the water equalizes and then
you cap your uh cap your Reservoir just
like on my machine over there and you're
going to take your electrodes you're
going to take your electricity whether
you're doing it from a generator whether
you're doing it from a solar panel a
windmill generator something like that
if you're using a windmill generator I
encourage you to use a battery I'm not a
fan of batteries but windmill generators
go up and down and up and down and so
you want kind of an equalized battery uh
or equalized voltage take that power and
you plug it on here positive
negative and you just let it go you just
let it go if you're collecting your
hydrogen you run it over to your
hydrogen collector a couple of 55 gallon
drums or something like that um and you
just watch the uh you just watch the
mineral content as it builds up in your
uh as it builds up your Reservoir in the
reservoir here it's going to
get excuse me it's going to get darker
and darker as the element content builds
up and it looks like rust it's not rust
like I said we're not disintegrating
plates we've madej the plates we're not
disintegrating and it's basically the
same thing going on in this main chamber
yes as is going on in the reservoir
that's right because the two are
connected in the way that that we've
described the two are going to basically
be equal there may be a little bit more
concentration in here that hasn't
traveled over to your Reservoir but
that's okay when you say Let It Go are
you talking hours days
or
um the concentration that you see here
is
probably
uh about 24 hours worth of uh worth of
running from start to finish with uh
with clear with with a clear additive
and the seed the seed elements 24 hours
so um whether that's uh that was off a
solar panel so that was
about 3 days worth maybe 4 days worth of
sunlight okay because of the W because
of the clouds and stuff like that if
you're running a pure DC Source from a
from a generator or something it's going
to be 24 hours and you're going to
you're going to see a significant
deposit over there um I I don't I
haven't felt impressed to just leave it
there okay I don't want it to short out
my plates I don't want it to build up so
high I want to drain it off and and and
and collect it I've got barrels and
barrels of it now got to figure out
where to put it or where to take it you
know so so the matter of uh taking off
the the uh that's very simple very
simple to do if you have a reservoir
it's even simpler if you have this
configuration because you just undo that
and pour it into a gallon jug if you
have a reservoir you just unhook it from
where you're where you're working and
pour it out into a gallon jug and then
put it back in place and start again so
very simple very simple way um see the
video from Tesla Tech my presentation
and I've got a picture of it on the wall
a very simple system with the reservoir
and the hydrogen column there or the the
bubbling column there and the flashback
arrester and and you can get a good
visual of it why do I I keep on
forgetting about that it's it looks just
like that very simple just pour it down
the way you go okay you can you could
even have a pigtail off of here with a
little valve that allows you to open it
pour it out and go with that um I always
think about those things after I'm done
building I oh shoot well that'd be
really nice right there but we don't
have it so we'll try this so how much
seed what's up how much
seed um I put a what do you see here
started out I've never added more I
started out with about a bottle of my
electric water and a um about 3 or 4
ounces of the gold and platinum okay and
it just keeps on keeps on breeding you
know um but for uh I'd start out with uh
um heck you could even oh that's
interesting idea you could even just mix
up a batch of Black Sands and and put
that and pour that in there of course
then you get a lot of iron oxide and we
don't want that so never mind forget I
said that
um it it it it's it's an experimental
thing we're just just going to we're
going to experiment and see I mean I'm
sure that there are people that go out
and buy collodial silver and pour it in
this
thing going
to okay anyway moving right along what's
that exactly yeah so uh remember my
lesson that I I mentioned earlier from
Alchemy
silver if you look at the Bible silver
is currency gold is never currency
silver is currency gold is for ceremony
and Enlightenment the silver medals are
for are for making money
Alchemists are forbidden from using gold
to to make themselves wealthy Nicholas
Fel made two batches of gold at like
four or five pounds each he gave it all
away every bit of it built churches
built orphanages built roads he made
silver and kept himself he lived in the
same house his parents gave him all his
life he never went he did travel and
study and learn but he didn't elevate
status gold to elevate your status you
will get a hammer from the universe
everyone that's tried it has so Platinum
Platinum is a little bit different you
can sell platinum but here here's a
little here's a little uh here's a
little secret Platinum is platinum makes
an adamantine
Warrior uh stanlee did not create the
idea of adamantium with you know
Wolverine skeleton and stuff like that
adamant
adamant is referenced in an
1820s Alchemist Masonic handbook they
referenced it as the indestructible of
the the indestructible metal of the
Atlantean Alchemists it was made from a
it's a composite of platinum and steel
Alloys that we cannot reproduce today
they have found rivets and coffins of
these thing made out of this stuff can't
even reproduce it it had to be
alchemical so anyway they date back they
date back to record before recorded
history so anyway you bleed off your gas
and you say you put it in 55 gallon
drone is there a specific gravity that
with this gas where you can Bleed It Out
Tank my my apologies I I I had I have
that in my lecture but I had to skip
over that because we were out of time
it's a 55 gallon drum with a 35 gallon
drum inserted into it and you fill it
with with with bottom cutout and you
fill it with water so that as the
hydrogen fills it up it pushes the the
the 35 Gall drum up and you have
grounding straps in it you have
stainless steel strips inside and out
riveted in place and then grounding
straps out there so no no no static can
build up as you're doing it that's how I
store hydrogen and uh hydrogen and
oxygen excuse me and that way I can use
it without pressurizing it if you
pressurize Browns gas you will die over
100 PSI it's uh at any point over 100
PSI can explode uh I've seen it done up
to 60 to eject into a
Turbocharger but anything over 100 is is
fatally dangerous lay around like
propane
um that's outside the scope of this but
the longer you let it sit the weaker it
becomes you have a question yeah uh
talking about the intentions and what
about if you're creating these metals to
finance research and development of
clean energy sources this is a this is a
beautiful and Noble
purpose the issue thatat that what if
you're using the metals that you're
creating to finance um research and
development of clean energy sources or
other Noble um benevolent um and that
actually fits with Alchemy that's one of
the purposes of alchemy um uh fulcanelli
went to the researchers in France right
before World War II who are trying to
build the atomic bomb and he said what
you're doing will destroy this planet
Alchemy is the only answer to stop it
that's recorded in uh in the scientific
journals there fenelli is one of the
greatest Alchemists of Europe uh in the
last century but
um you can do that and it's a kin to uh
it's akin to Nicholas Fel using the uh
his alchemical his alchemical metal
Creations to fund more of his research
into Alchemy and immortality so you can
do that the problem arises when
you get people with egos involved okay a
huge amount of money in
research uh let's say $100,000 is
devoted to research into something and I
know this from personal experience
$55,000 of it goes to the researcher and
a huge amount of money goes to the
administrative costs okay that's the
same thing as uh as as profits so you
have to be very careful with the spirit
of the people involved D once the spirit
once you get gold
involved
oh um what what is the quote um when
gold is involved the laws of God and men
are are set at not that was Nicholas Fel
when gold is involved the laws of God
and men are said it not expand just a
little bit what this means is
um anybody heard of Gold Fever oh yeah
that's the short term yes Gold
Fever The the gold gold people know that
gold is is the most is is a
representation of a higher level of
Consciousness okay but people that don't
resonate at a higher level of
Consciousness see it as something that
they want to obtain at any cost and so
and gold can be considered to be wealth
gold can be considered to be power
usually gold is considered to be the
yellow metal um and
so they desire this and they will do
anything that it takes to obtain it and
and and control it and so I mean I've
seen people shot not over the gold but
over the the possibility of gold exactly
so what you have to do is you have to
find people who will rise above that
it's like I was talking to somebody
earlier I have I have held an ele I have
held a rock in my hand it's a White Rock
and it's and it looks like nothing and
if I held a pound of that and a pound of
gold in my hand and an angel or one of
you or somebody came up and said throw
one of them away I'd throw away the gold
in a heartbeat because the rock is an
element that contains so much power for
healing and energy and health and and
betterment of the world that the that
the yellow metal will never be okay well
that it could be but but this is in its
raw form and we can use it so much
better so that's what I would do so um
when you start dealing with research and
development and uh bringing in bringing
it making alchemical uh money for uh
putting that towards uh research and
development you have to make certain
that there's nobody skimming out of the
Coffer there's no egos involved that
it's really the people that are working
on it that absolutely need it that are
getting it or you just start playing
with silver and you're
okay what about radioactive elements H
radioactive elements are touchy I
haven't tried any of that because I
don't like playing with radioactive
elements
um I will tell you this I don't know if
I've said it before in a lecture or not
but uh radioactivity everything
conductivity radioactivity magnetism
comes down to Crystal and geometrical
structure Nica Tesla theorized that
radioactivity was a manifestation of
cosmic rays interacting with with let's
say uranium a radioactive Rock um was uh
radiation was the result of cosmic r is
interacting with it and if we could
Shield it properly the radiation would
go away so a friend of his didn't agree
with this at all and wanted to prove him
wrong about 20 years later he had the
opportunity and they were drilling one
of the deepest deepest holes on the
entire planet I think they went down
18,000 ft and this gentleman was
involved with it he wanted to prove
Tesla wrong and so he took a radioactive
powerful radioactive sample and strapped
a uh a a counter probe to it and lowered
it down into this hole
and he got down about 16,000 ft and the
meter that they've got up there it's
just
buzzing because it's right next to the
sample you get down 16,000 ft and it
turns
off what that shows is that the
crystallin structure of the metal is is
interacting with the Rays that are
hitting the planet and when it got down
to about 16,000 ft it was no longer
interacting with those Rays anymore and
it wasn't a matter of a cord getting
disconnected no no when they pulled it
back up hit about uh actually they got
it back up and it stopped buzzing and it
took about 2 hours for that sample to
start generating radiation
again so it has everything to do with
energy coming in which actually tells us
something very interesting if we can
create I mean that's radio that's that's
energy coming out of that that sample if
we can find the proper crystalling
geometrical structure Mike Wendell is
actually working on this in a in a
little bit different way we we can
actually
you know we could actually create a
plate or a substance with the proper
crystallin structure that take that make
all the energy we could ever want from
cosmic radiation cosmic rays okay um the
day night solar cell is an example of
this so just something to just something
to experiment with so that's why um we
can remediate nuclear radiation with
proper Browns gas not the not the the
weak stuff but the good stuff um it dis
it
um changes the entire Crystal and
structure of the material so that it is
no longer responding to the cosmic rays
uh we did an experiment with uh some
cold electricity stuff that you know we
we hooked up a cold electricity
generator to a caducus wand and we ran
it over some powerful uh um Alpha
radiation samples and it would they
completely uh all the radiation went
away for about 30 minutes
so and then it slowly came back so
there's different ways to do it um
radiation is not the boogeyman that uh
uh the governments and the universities
and highbrow people of the world would
like us to believe it is I mean it's
dangerous don't get me wrong but you can
get rid of it in many different ways but
that's another story entirely I'm sorry
I digress a lot let's summarize I've got
seven minutes left on my battery I've
got more on my tape but
um in this setting since it'll be hard
to get back into the let's go ahead and
wrap it up kind of describing the
process and and the mechanism and give
us a take home lesson what we are doing
is we are utilizing
a uh hydrogen electrolysis
cell just like this well wet cell versus
dry cell but same principle we're using
a hydrogen electrolysis cell we are
seeding it with
elements we use the the hydrogen and
oxygen that comes off for whatever
purposes we want whether it be power or
heat generation and our byproduct that's
going to collect in the bottom as as the
more we run is elements that we sh it
with and what we are looking at is the
ability to take hydrogen and oxygen
imprint a template on them and order the
energy into physical reality literally
electricity becoming uh becoming
physical reality and if and if if we
want to you know debate numbers I I'll
just throw this out there in 1 cubic
cm of the vacuum there exists enough
energy to power the United States for an
entire year so if we are working with
the implosion and the and the changes of
hydrogen and oxygen that we experience
in in a hydrolysis cell how much energy
are we actually playing with from the
vacuum so that's i' like to leave you
with basically Elemental copy machine
Elemental copy machine is a good way to
put it powered by the motors of the
universe so there we go any final um
questions from the audience before we
does it still uh act as a copier or if
you don't ignite the gas oh you don't
have to ignite the
gas no not I've never ignite I'm not
igniting any of this no you're still
storing it for a future use well I
that's that's uh but that's over here in
this system I can I I have just blood
this off just into the atmosphere one go
ahead when you say salt water would you
say like salt sea water or just sodium
chloride that we table salt thank you
for for asking that I would not
recommend using Straight salt water I
would only use sea water um I'm going to
build an entirely different machine to
use seawat in because I don't want to
run I don't want to mess this one up I
like playing with it forther with them
all my other stuff um only seawater
saltwater Brian from oil wells uh the
Great Salt Lake water Great Salt Lake is
a fantastic source of very interesting
elements um never never straight
saltwater salt water you're going to
pour off a huge amount of of chlorine
gas and uh really bad stuff so thank you
for bringing that up thank you for
clarifying that okay any other final
comments
questions what he says go ahead actually
measure the amount of gas that comes off
versus the number the ounces of water
that you're
disassociated you have far more
hydrogen and oxygen than is in the ounce
of water yeah thank you I didn't even so
the hydrogen and oxygen is also
alchemical hydrogen and oxygen um there
are on the back of your hand you do the
calculations you you you mentioned how
much you were getting off uhhuh and you
talked a little bit you just he just
said well there not much water right not
much water if you do back on the back of
your hand you can do the calculations
how much is a mold of
water in hydrogen and oxygen it's well
known and then you can measure the
hydrogen oxygen that you
have yeah I was completely forgotten
about that it's about 16 times
yeah and that was the thing was kev's
articles about so is it possible that
the electris of the water is not
necessarily the crucial ingredient but
that the it sets us a context of copying
that includes copying the water the the
hydrogen and oxygen and whatever other
elements are in the
water to support what he says the
Japanese uh uh nuclear physicist forgive
me I forgotten his name he was
responsible for their uh the nuclear
regulatory agency in in Japan he ran
their their laboratory he got talked
into doing this and so he ran the
test took iron electrodes just straight
iron electrodes 999
pure and did exactly what you done took
the water measured the amount of
hydrogen and oxygen and when he got far
more
than was supposed but then uh they spent
three or four pages in the article
trying to say what was happening at the
molecular level when they got
through there was no
conclusion this one of three or four
different possible ways but
they all right so well we're almost out
of time I I'd like to I'd like to finish
that TR bring it back here real quick um
water separates into steam at 1,800 to
one volume okay so one liter of water
will create 1,800 L of steam good Browns
gas will and so we use that as a rule of
thumb and then that's that's where these
figures come from what we would expect
to find but good Browns gas can produce
much much more volume than just the 1800
to1 so that's what we're saying where is
that coming from I completely forgot
about that work exactly it proves
exactly what you're saying exactly so um
this device uh as as was mentioned
earlier this device produces about um 20
lers of of gas an hour and so it's not a
huge volume but over time 20 L of gas an
hour for an 8 Hour sunny day definitely
enough uh gas to cook cook meals and
maybe even heat a house if you're uh and
I'm going to use it to heat my shop this
summer or this winter so um there are
many many facets of this and many
applications and and I encourage
everybody to jump in feet first and
experiment with it and see where it goes
because as we've seen from Al and other
people that talked uh U this week and
and uh there other experiments this is
being proved out over and over again now
it's time to actually focus on it and
see where we can take it because water
is the future of this planet if we don't
find ways to more effectively utilize
our water you know we're not we're not
going to make it so thank you very much
for all your time and everything thanks
for being here and the questions all